<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Richard Lewis</title>
    <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Richard Lewis</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 00:00:56 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.gogorichie.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Azure Static Web Apps: The Cloud&#39;s New Electric Vehicle</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/azurespringcleaning2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 00:00:56 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/azurespringcleaning2023/</guid>
      <description>Write blog post here. https://gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/azurespringcleaning2023/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Azure Synapse Overview</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/azure-synapse-overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 08:46:19 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/azure-synapse-overview/</guid>
      <description>Earlier this year I joined the Azure Synapse Influencer Program. But I don&amp;rsquo;t receive payments as an influencer instead I get a wide range of benefits, such as early access to new features and capabilities, access to exclusive training and resources, and opportunities to engage with the Azure Synapse product team and also the occasional free swag like a coffee cup and sticker. I joined the program to build my knowledge around the platform and be able to show its value of it to my clients.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Devops Days Chicago 2022 Recap</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/devopsdayschicago2022recap/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 07:24:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/devopsdayschicago2022recap/</guid>
      <description>I had the opportunity to attend another DevOps Days Chicago which is a regional conference focused on software development, IT infrastructure operations, and the intersection between them called DevOps. This was the fourth DevOps days I have attended, third in person, and first as a speaker. Speaking of which it’s good to be able to get back to a conference in person. I’m an extrovert so I love meeting new people and don’t get that really from virtual conferences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts On Azure Cache For Redis</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/thoughts-on-azure-cache-4-redis/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 08:46:19 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/thoughts-on-azure-cache-4-redis/</guid>
      <description>Recently I took some time to revisit Azure Cache for Redis I got first introduced to the service in 2018 and a lot has changed since then. I won’t go into detail about Redis and what it is or What is caching. But instead, I want to share my thoughts on using it on the Azure platform.
A particular use benefit of using Azure Cache for Redis instead of the self-hosting version for data cache needs is it will allow a business to bring the frequently called data to the cloud so that the data can be called faster with higher availability.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ubiquiti Unifi Setup Iteration Four</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/ubiquiti-unifi-setup-iteration-four/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 17:05:31 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/ubiquiti-unifi-setup-iteration-four/</guid>
      <description>Recap
This is a continuation of my 2020 network overhaul. You can read the details about how this project started at this link. I ended the updates to my home network in 2020 in a good place and by that I mean everything was running smoothly with the full network being managed by software. There were no issues but lot’s of opportunities for improvement. So that left me thinking my 2021 improvements would be focused on reducing dependencies on 3rd party cloud services such as Ring and Google Nest cameras.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taking My Security Grade From D to A</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/security-grade/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 20:21:20 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/security-grade/</guid>
      <description>Backstory
For my website, security has always been a second-class citizen I&amp;rsquo;ve never treated it fairly outside of the basic practices of an SSL certificate and patching of the host and any plugins I might be using. I had the opportunity to join Scott Hanselman for a small group session hosted by my company and one of the things he talked about was providing server-side security and sound of mind to users.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terrafy Knowledge Share</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/terrafyknowledge/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 22:46:02 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/terrafyknowledge/</guid>
      <description>A little disclaimer here, these are notes from a live demo on 4-28-22 sorry if this doesn&amp;rsquo;t make sense later.
Overview:
Azure Terrafy is a new tool currently in preview as of April 27th from Microsoft designed to help you export Azure Resources listed within the AzureRM provider to a terraform main.tf file and maintain a state file.
How To Install It:
To be able to install Terrafy you&amp;rsquo;ll need to download the binary from the github repo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DevOps Days Birmingham Alabama 2022 Talk</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/devopsdaysbham-2022-talk/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/devopsdaysbham-2022-talk/</guid>
      <description>Thanks for attending my talk on LMAO Helps During Outages at DevOps Days Birmingham 2022. As promised in the talk i wanted to share my slides for all. For those who missed my talk but stumbled across this post. My talk was about solving the problem of when your company has an outage but there is no need to sweat just remember to LMAO and you’ll get through it having a combination of logs, metrics, alerts, and an observability tool in place will help your company LOL through it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Professional Technical Interviewee Guest Appearance</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/professional-technical-interviewee-appearance/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/professional-technical-interviewee-appearance/</guid>
      <description>A few months back had the opportunity to joined my friend Taylor Dorsett on his Podcast to talk about Professional Technical Interviews from a DevOps perspective. If you&amp;rsquo;re interested in the DevOps space this is a great conversation to listen. Be sure to check it out over on his Youtube channel Professional Technical Interviewee with Taylor Dorsett.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Notifications on Certificate Expiration Dates Using Azure Key Vault</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/keyvault-handlingsslcert/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2021 11:45:53 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/keyvault-handlingsslcert/</guid>
      <description>Back in July fellow Azure blogger Billy York wrote a blog post about Monitoring SSL certificates with Azure monitor utilizing a standard test within App Insights, it&amp;rsquo;s really cool that Azure finally added this ability. I want to talk about an alternative less known method using Azure Key Vault certificate contacts and lifetime contacts.
What is Azure Key Vault? For those who are unfamiliar with The Azure service Azure Key Vault the fastest way to sum it up is that its a cloud service on Azure used for storing sensitive application information like tokens, passwords, API keys as well as TLS and SSL certificates used by resources on Azure or accessing Azure resources.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My 2020 Ubiquiti Unifi Setup</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/my-2020-ubiquiti-unifi-setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2021 23:05:31 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/my-2020-ubiquiti-unifi-setup/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been using Ubiquiti products since late 2018 to improve the wireless experience of my wife in our townhouse. I came across the product line while trying to solve the problem of getting decent wire coverage across a 2500 Sq foot two-story townhouse. I tried mesh network products from Netgear, Google, and some other companies always with the same problem repeaters would fail, the handoff between access points was awful, and most importantly the quality of service was crap leaving my wife frustrated.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/hello_world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 22:49:37 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/hello_world/</guid>
      <description>First post using Hugo</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Richard!</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2020 23:53:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Richard is a highly skilled and experienced IT professional with over 20 years of experience in the industry. With a focus on process improvement through automation, he has expertise in the practice of DevOps, which involves delivering high-quality software through a combination of people, processes, and products. Throughout his career, Richard has worked with a wide range of IT organizations, from startups to Fortune 500 companies, and has learned from some of the best in the industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Favorite VSCode Plugins Of 2019</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/2019_fav_vscode_plugins/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2019 23:53:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/2019_fav_vscode_plugins/</guid>
      <description>2019 was a big year for me using VS Code before the beginning of the year I was still using Notepad++ along with Visual Studio as my daily IDE&amp;rsquo;s. But in January I tried to use VS Code every day for 30 days and I haven&amp;rsquo;t stopped and along the way, I also convinced a few of my Co-workers to convert over as well. I remember reading the 2018 Stack Overflow release their annual Developer survey results last December, one of the interesting things that I noticed was that VS Code had risen to the top as the Most Popular Development Environment among Developers and Admins with 35% of 75,398 respondents claiming to use it which is pretty cool for a tool-less than 5 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Code Nation: The Future Of Tomorrow</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/the-future-of-tomorrow/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2019 22:49:37 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/the-future-of-tomorrow/</guid>
      <description>Part my role at Coyote involves me work with community orginzations. In early 2019 Coyote&amp;rsquo;s Software Development group became involved with Code Nation, an 501c3 organization based out of New York, which is focused on equipping students, in under-resourced high schools, with the skills, experiences, and connections that give them access to careers in technology.
Code Nation’s approach is using a volunteer teaching corp of hundreds of professional web and software developers, that provide tuition-free coding courses and work-based learning programs to students of these under-resourced schools.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Daily Grind Guest Appearance</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/daily-grind-interview/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/daily-grind-interview/</guid>
      <description>Earlier this month I dropped by my friend Kelly Johnson&amp;rsquo;s podcast she is just starting up The Daily Grind Podcast check out our conversation as we talk about Pickleball, Jaycees, Software Conferences, and what i do as a Developer Advocate.
Click here to subscribe</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What WordPress Plugins am I using in 2017?</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2017-11-01-what-wordpress-plugins-am-i-using/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2017 16:31:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2017-11-01-what-wordpress-plugins-am-i-using/</guid>
      <description>It’s been four years since I wrote my last update about what plugins I’m using on my WordPress platform. I’ve gotten more simple about the plugins and what I need them to do for me. Last time I wrote a post about the plugins their were seven and now I’m only running five.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I Jaycee</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/jci/why_i_jaycee/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 15:43:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/jci/why_i_jaycee/</guid>
      <description>The second week of October annually is Jaycee Week, it&amp;rsquo;s the week where we as Jaycees celebrate the founding of our organization in 1915 by Henry Giessenbier Jr. Ironically this month marks my 14th year as a member. So what better time of the year than now to share with you why I Jaycee? I joined the Jaycees to help make my community a better place. But I stay a Jaycee because it gives me the opportunity to be a Young Active Citizen, who can create positive change within my community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Favorite Salesforce Tools</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2014-10-27-my-favorite-salesforce-tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2014 07:38:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2014-10-27-my-favorite-salesforce-tools/</guid>
      <description>Last year I came across a post by Sharif Shaalan on his blog Salesforce.com Tips, Tricks, Solutions, and Thoughts talking about his favorite Salesforce Tools he uses quite often and I really enjoyed his posting, so I thought I would share my favorite tools. Salesforce.com prides it’s self as a “No Software” company meaning everything you need to get up and running is in the product and platform. Well you may not need software to get up and running on Salesforce but it takes great tools to keep to running smooth and efficient.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Experience with Freedompop</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2014-08-20-my-experience-with-freedompop/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2014 18:56:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2014-08-20-my-experience-with-freedompop/</guid>
      <description>I live outside of Chicago so there are a lot of options for mobile high speed internet. My cellular carrier is Sprint which has amazing LTE service and I’m getting on average 24Mbps down but there tethering plan is not worth the monthly cost for my usage. I first heard about Freedompop via a podcast called Tech News Today a couple of years ago so I started to get familiar with it back then but really didn’t have a need for it at the time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monitor Your Salesforce Instance Via An Automated Email</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2014-03-04-monitor-your-salesforce-instance-via-an-automated-email/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2014 15:29:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2014-03-04-monitor-your-salesforce-instance-via-an-automated-email/</guid>
      <description>One of the challenges I face within Salesforce is noticing performance issues before my users do. It doesn’t happen to often but when it does my users notice. Like any other system Salesforce is only as weak as its weakest link. To help me stay ahead without constantly having to look at trust.salesforce.com I’ve created a zap using Zapier to monitor the rss feed for my server and send me a email when an incident is reported though the rss feed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>T-SQL Tuesday 050: Automation, Get Work Done While Sleeping</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/sql/t-sql-tuesday-50/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/sql/t-sql-tuesday-50/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been a while since I&amp;rsquo;ve written a #tsql2sday post, but thought that this month&amp;rsquo;s topic was worthy of me hoping into the pool with the #sqlfamily. This month the subject is &amp;ldquo;Automation&amp;rdquo;. chosen by Hemanth D. (Blog | @SqlChow). If you want to read the opening post, please click the image above. I&amp;rsquo;m lover of software automation and been a fan since writing my first macro in Excel when I was in high school.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Favorite Salesforce Blogs</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2013-12-12-my-favorite-salesforce-blogs/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2013 12:13:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2013-12-12-my-favorite-salesforce-blogs/</guid>
      <description>I love to learn and talk SQL all day everyday which gave me the inspiration for my blog post about my favorite SSIS Reference Points and my Favorite Business Intelligence Blogs in the past. So without further adieu I present to my list of what I blogs I commonly read in the Salesforce area and of course there in no particular order. I’ve built on the platform and written functions around it off and on over the last 4 years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>St. Judes &amp;#038; Me</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2013-12-04-st-judes-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2013 10:06:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2013-12-04-st-judes-me/</guid>
      <description>Each I give my time and money to many causes. The way I handle giving my time and money to causes is simple. Through the Jaycees I’m able to give my time to many causes in the way of service to my local community and of course my favorite is Hospital Care-a-van which was run by the Mount Prospect Jaycees. Now as for money, each year I pick a different organization I’m interested in and give my money to them and I ask my friends to join in and support me in making an impact in that organizations cause.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DreamForce 2013 Wrapup</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/dreamforce2013/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/dreamforce2013/</guid>
      <description>This year I made the trip to San Francisco for Salesforce&amp;rsquo;s annual DreamForce a five day conference that trumps all other conference. Every aspect of the event was amazing and WOW 120,000 attendees. The leadership speaker series, the trainings, the networking opportunities, and the parties were all great. My highlights and most memorable moments were getting to meet a couple of vendors that I only get to speak with on the phone including one who is located in France.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spring Cleaning 2013</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2013-05-28-spring-cleaning/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2013 15:29:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2013-05-28-spring-cleaning/</guid>
      <description>It’s a couple of months since my last post and even longer since I’ve logged into the backend of my site. So this morning I did a lot admining of my site, kicked the morning off by removing a bunch of old plugins, old backups, and decided to take the twenty twelve theme for a test drive. While I’m at it’s been two years since my original posting on which wordpress plugin I use.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Practices For Automating Business Processes with Kapow</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/rpa/best-practices-for-automating-business-processes-with-kapow/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/rpa/best-practices-for-automating-business-processes-with-kapow/</guid>
      <description>Thanks for attending my session on best practices for automation business processes with Kapow at the 2013 Kapow.Wow User Summit. As promised in the session i wanted to share my slides for all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Limit Yourself</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2013-02-06-why-limit-yourself/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2013 11:41:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2013-02-06-why-limit-yourself/</guid>
      <description>We join the Jaycees so that we can grow as individuals, expand ourselves personally, and to help humanity. Part of growing ourselves is taking advantage of all the opportunities that we’re presented with in life. Your membership to our great organization allows you many opportunities to do things that you can only dreamed of. You can drive positive change in your community and around the world. You can help build a park for neighborhood kids, you help fight diseases around the world, and you can meet world leaders and discuss your thoughts on global issues.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Four Component Approach</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/jci/the-four-component-approach/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/jci/the-four-component-approach/</guid>
      <description>The Jaycees as you all know by now is more than just a community service organization. Since the founding in 1915 it has held true to its primary purpose of building young leaders to tackle the challenges of tomorrow. In 2013 I will be servicing you as your State Membership Development vice President; the Member Development area encompasses four key components and all them vital. First Recruit since our organization is based on membership requirements it’s important that we replace those that no longer meet our requirements to be members.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10 Apps I Loved In 2012</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2012-12-31-10-apps-i-loved-in-2012/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2012 09:20:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2012-12-31-10-apps-i-loved-in-2012/</guid>
      <description>Now that we’re in the final day of 2012 I figure it was a great time to toast the apps that make my life easier throughout the year. These apps are crossed platform you can use them and their services on both Android, IPhone, and in some cases Blackberry.
Tripit Evernote Spotify Hulu Netflix Flipboard Gasbuddy Amazon Kindle Reader Xbox 360 Smartglass Ride Metra </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started With Microsoft Access</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/sql/getting-started-with-microsoft-access/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/sql/getting-started-with-microsoft-access/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been using Microsoft Access since Access 97 it&amp;rsquo;s a very powerful tool is you use it right. You can use it for everything from personal Baseball card inventory control to managing home inventories; even fortune 500 companies use it to manage million dollar systems. As I said if you use it right it can be quite a powerful tool built on some amazing framework. Recently a friend who&amp;rsquo;s getting into access asked me if I could provide him some resources so that he can get better familiar with the tool.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intro To Kapow Katalyst</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/rpa/intro-to-kapow-katalyst/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/rpa/intro-to-kapow-katalyst/</guid>
      <description>This will be the first posting of a new category on my blog regard Kapow Software a Robotic Process Automation (RPA) tool. Before I begin to discuss my usage experiences and technical information regarding Kapow Katalyst, I figure it would be good to give a little background about it. Kapow Katalyst is a Web Data Aggregation Tool; these tools are used to capture data from websites for analytic&amp;rsquo;s purposes. Where Kapow excels is it allows you to complete your ETL process from a single execution aka a Robot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Passion</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2012-11-20-my-passion/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2012 14:37:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2012-11-20-my-passion/</guid>
      <description>When I interviewed with Coyote a discussion came up of passion and I said my passion at work was turning data into insight for my coworkers. During my presentation about myself to our Executive team and my coworkers I realized what my true passion is… it’s to help people. Every job I’ve had involved helping people and at Coyote it’s no different I’m just using my technical skills to help our coworkers and our customers; outside work I love to volunteer with the Jaycees because we help people and make an impact with the work we do around the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WHS Just Chugging Along</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2012-11-20-whs-just-chugging-along/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2012 13:51:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2012-11-20-whs-just-chugging-along/</guid>
      <description>It’s true when they say no news is good news, my Windows Home Server has been just chugging along currently were approaching 180 days without rebooting, which is quite impressive to even to me. Actually now that think about it I made a major change to my setup back in March. I purchased a Dell PowerEdge 700 for 25 dollars on eBay which a real server instead of an old desktop I had lying around.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Querying The Most Recent Records</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/sql/querying-the-most-recent-records/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/sql/querying-the-most-recent-records/</guid>
      <description>Here’s another fun solution for you business intelligence people out there. Suppose you wanted to pull data that was updated in the last 15mins based on when a row was last. I&amp;rsquo;m sure there are many ways to accomplish this but I like to use the DATEADD() function in Microsoft SQL Server 2008. Below is the query using the AdventureWorks2008R2 database enjoy.
SELECT I.ProductID, I.LocationID, I.Bin, I.Shelf, I.Quantity, P.ProductNumber, P.Name, I.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Serving As 2013 State Vice President</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2012-09-12-2013statevp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2012 10:06:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2012-09-12-2013statevp/</guid>
      <description>On September 8th my campaign to serve the Illinois Jaycees members as their 2013 Membership Development Vice President came to end with me being elected. It’s true competing for the time of our members has gotten tougher each year our chapter, region, and state boards have gotten stretched too thin, burned out quickly, not adequately trained and weaker. As a result our members have suffered. Next year I want to focus on shaping the future of our organization.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A New Journey</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2012-09-05-new-journey/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2012 09:37:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2012-09-05-new-journey/</guid>
      <description>August 20th was my last day at Sears Holdings. I once heard somewhere the average person my age spends three years at a job before leaving and move on. Well I sent 12 years there of course I held four different roles there during that time. I decided to leave Sears Holdings because the opportunity presented to me to join Coyote Logistics and learn &amp;amp; develop new systems was too great to pass up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wheeling Jaycees Social Media 101</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2012-07-29-social-media-101/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jul 2012 19:33:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2012-07-29-social-media-101/</guid>
      <description>Every wonder why some people have amazing looking Facebook profiles or 1000s of followers? In this 30 minute session we will discuss how to use facebook, google+, twitter the simple and easy way to communicate with your friends, family, and followers. This course is led me Richard Lewis a veteran user of social media sites and Chairman of the US Jaycees National Technology Advisory Committee. Come out next month on August 7th at 7:00PM.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SQL Saturday 119 Recap In 189 Words</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/sql/sql-saturday-119-recap-in-189-words/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/sql/sql-saturday-119-recap-in-189-words/</guid>
      <description>So I&amp;rsquo;m about a month late or maybe three in writing my recap on the event so here goes. It was awesomeness !!!! 2012 marked my second SQL Saturday that I&amp;rsquo;ve attended and have to say it just keeps getting better. This year I was able to volunteer with registration which is an awesome way to meet all the attendees well at least most of them. Also I hooped into five awesome sessions &amp;ldquo;A Complete BI Solution in About an Hour!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>April Meme 15 Assignment</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/sql/april-meme15-assignment/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/sql/april-meme15-assignment/</guid>
      <description>Another #Meme 15 topic brought you by MVP Jason Strate (Blog | twitter). This month topic &amp;ldquo;What are ten blogs that you think other SQL Server professionals should be following but might not be?&amp;rdquo; Coming up with a list of just 10 is harder than I thought narrowing it down to ten is just way to hard but i was able to do. The list I put together covers everyone from the newbie to SQL to the all-round DBA.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Living the Windows 8 Experience</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2012-03-24-living-the-windows-8-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2012 21:43:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2012-03-24-living-the-windows-8-experience/</guid>
      <description>Introduction
I downloaded Windows 8 when it was released to Developers back last year and installed it on a virtual workstation with a 2 gigs of ram running from my Windows Home Server. I thought it was shaky and slow. So I decided to abandon it. Until recently when the Consumer Preview release came out and I decided to give it another try. Getting windows 8 up running was actually quite simple.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick &amp; Simple Inner Join</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/sql/quick-simple-inner-join/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/sql/quick-simple-inner-join/</guid>
      <description>A business partner approached me the other day looking to share information with my company. Since parts numbers are recycled more often than lame jokes in my business one of the things we needed the business partner to provide was the brand of the part. The business partner said that this would be difficult to do since they were unfamiliar with linking data across tables in any manner. After understanding a little about the setup of the partner&amp;rsquo;s tables I taught them to design a view linking the two primary tables where the data could be seen together through a view.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meme 15 Why Did I Start Blogging</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/sql/why-did-i-start-blogging/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/sql/why-did-i-start-blogging/</guid>
      <description>This month&amp;rsquo;s Meme15 assignment and the first was chosen by Jason Strate (Blog|Twitter) he posed the assignment of writing about why do I blog and why I started.
I started blogging back in 2003 just about a one year after launching Gogorichie.com, back then it was the social network of its time along with AIM and YIM. As me and my high school friends went off to college we stayed in contact via our blogs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>T-SQL Tuesday 025 - My Favorite Little Trick</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/sql/my-favorite-little-trick/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/sql/my-favorite-little-trick/</guid>
      <description>This month&amp;rsquo;s T-SQL Tuesday topic is from Allen White. He posed the question of what is my favorite little SQL trick. I can&amp;rsquo;t wait to see what tips the #SQLFamily write about. I discovered one of my favorite tricks last year, just a little background my first SQL version I started out administrating and developing on 8 years ago was SQL 2000 back then to get table statistics was no easy task.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meme Monday: What SQLFamily Means To Me</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/sql/sqlfamily-means-to-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/sql/sqlfamily-means-to-me/</guid>
      <description>I saw this topic a few weeks back on @sqlrockstar&amp;rsquo;s site but never got around to writing a post.
I&amp;rsquo;ve been in working on databases for about 6 years now a mixture of Access, SQL, Teradata, and MySQL. So when I saw the topic thoughts began to flow through my brain. What does the SQL Family mean to me?? it means that there is a network of people with the same interest, challenged by the same problems as me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nothing But Nets News Flash !!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2011-11-02-nothing-but-nets-news-flash/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2011 18:34:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2011-11-02-nothing-but-nets-news-flash/</guid>
      <description>Great News Everyone, I talked to Anthony Colletti today via email. He’s in Brussels Belgium at the JCI World Congress and said that were *#3 in the
WORLD* for JCI organizations in raising money for Nothing But Nets !!!!! just think how much more we can achieve by the end of the year. For every $10 we raise we save a life from Malaria donate at http://bit.ly/ut25Oh
Richard Lewis
2011 Website Program Manager – United States Jaycees</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nothing But Nets Fundraising Update</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2011-09-14-nothing-but-nets-fundraising-update-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2011 10:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2011-09-14-nothing-but-nets-fundraising-update-2/</guid>
      <description>What an awesome GA we had this past weekend!!! Saturday during Lunch Anthony Colletti spoke about how close we are the our 2011 Nothing But Nets goal and our chapters STEPPED UP big time…to the tune of $1051.00 in pledges and donations. A big thanks goes out to all those chapters Mount Prospect, Gurnee/Lindenhurst, Bolingbrook, Chatham, Woodstock, Lombard, and Woodridge. Once we receive all the checks we will be only $289 away from our goal !</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bringing the T.K.O</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2011-09-05-bringing-the-t-k-o/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2011 09:43:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2011-09-05-bringing-the-t-k-o/</guid>
      <description>Last friday was exciting I announced my candidacy for 2012 Area One Vice President of the Illinois Jaycees. I believe that we can grow our area with outstanding Training held locally, We can use the Knowledge of our members and our networks to strengthen our area, and We can retain our members through all the Opportunities our organization have to offer. Like my page on Facebook at http://www.facebook.com/Voteforrichard and follow my campaign.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jaycees and Politics</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/jci/jaycees-and-politics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/jci/jaycees-and-politics/</guid>
      <description>As Jaycee members we have a long history of driving change in our communities across the country and all through our grassroots skills and efforts. For example, when a group of young business men in the Los Angeles area were dissatisfied with their representation in congress they sought out a candidate and came across a young who was a Jaycee their first reaction was here is a young man who has been through the best training in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Founding Of The Abbeville Jaycees</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/jci/abbeville-jaycees/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/jci/abbeville-jaycees/</guid>
      <description>Over the weekend I read another chapter of the book Young Men Can Change The World. I came across another great story this one of how the Abbeville Jaycees was founded. The story was a recount of the adventure of at the time U.S. Jaycees National Vice President Robert E. Condon who at the age of 29 also held the position of civil defense commissioner for the greater New York metro area.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Outstanding Young Farmers</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2011-05-13-outstanding-young-farmers/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2011 10:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2011-05-13-outstanding-young-farmers/</guid>
      <description>Since 1954 Outstanding Young Farmers has been a signature program of the US Jaycees and believe it or not we’ve got very little to do with. now i know that’s hard to believe that the largest Jaycee state and is covered by 80% of farm land hasn’t Produce an Outstanding Young Farmer since 2008. Well that changes this year, because our states goal is to submit 5 outstanding candidates for this award.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What’s Our Impact So Far</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2011-05-11-whats-our-impact-so-far/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2011 12:48:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2011-05-11-whats-our-impact-so-far/</guid>
      <description>As i write this i reflect back on January when State VP Geno asked me what was my Goal for Nothing But Nets? I pondered for a second and said I want to double what we made in 2010 and I wrote down $3000 dollars and then i started to wonder could we really do it? Well I’m excited to say that in just 5 months we’ve crossed the $3,000 dollar mark and were still going.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scholarship Opportunities</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2011-04-08-scholarship-opportunities/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2011 10:16:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2011-04-08-scholarship-opportunities/</guid>
      <description>By Richard Lewis
National Programs &amp;amp; Government Involvement State Chairmen
Richard.lewis@iljaycees.org
It’s that wonderful time of year if you’re a student the nice weather outside may signal the near end of another year and it’s the time when most Jaycee chapters give away there annual scholarship to students in their communities. But did you know that as a Jaycee member you and your family are eligible for FIVE scholarship programs funded by our organization?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Support Our Troops Update</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2011-04-04-support-our-troops-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2011 10:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2011-04-04-support-our-troops-update/</guid>
      <description>Want to win 100 bucks? This year’s National Chair for the Support Our Troops program has setup a facebook group to communicate challenges and project ideas to directly to chapter members.
She is running a challenge, she wants the chapters around country to send their completed CPG’s to her for projects they’ve ran this year by June 1st and she will give the best one selected One Hundred Bucks. Join her group at http://www.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meme Monday 4-4-11</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/sql/meme-monday-4-4-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/sql/meme-monday-4-4-11/</guid>
      <description>First off shout out to Thomas Larock for coming up with this idea. Today’s meme is “Write a SQL blog post in 11 words or less”, and here is my entry: Write query. Syntax error. Search Google. run query again. Happy dance!!!! Some more shout outs to my favorite readings from last month: * Pinal Dave (Blog | @pinaldave) * Brent Ozar (Blog | @BrentO) * Thomas Larock (Blog | @sqlrockstar) * BIDN (Blog | @bidn)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Remember To Vote</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2011-03-10-remember-to-vote/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2011 14:51:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2011-03-10-remember-to-vote/</guid>
      <description>I was reading a section of a Book called Young Men Can Change The World the other day and wanted to share it with you. It told the story of group Jaycee members out in California who were so passionate with some the legislation being passed in their community that they put together a committee to find someone from their community to run for Representative. After months of searching they found a young Jaycee member who was a lawyer and encouraged him to run, with their support and determination not to lose he went on to win and get elected.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Remember To Vote</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/jci/remember-to-vote/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/jci/remember-to-vote/</guid>
      <description>I was reading a section of a Book called Young Men Can Change The World the other day and wanted to share it with you. It told the story of group Jaycee members out in California who were so passionate with some the legislation being passed in their community that they put together a committee to find someone from their community to run for Representative. After months of searching they found a young Jaycee member who was a lawyer and encouraged him to run, with their support and determination not to lose he went on to win and get elected.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Impact Then and Now</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2011-02-11-our-impact-then-and-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2011 15:16:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2011-02-11-our-impact-then-and-now/</guid>
      <description>Richard Lewis
National Programs and Government Involvement State Chairmen In 1954 Jaycees from many nations provided medical relief to the hundreds of thousands of Vietnamese refugees fleeing North Viet Nam. This became one of our first big international projects; it was known as operation brotherhood and brought international attention to the US Jaycees and our international organization JCI around the globe. When I think of the line in our creed “The Brotherhood of man transcends the Sovereignty of Nations” It makes me think back about the Jaycee organization over the years and our acceptances of each other and our commitment to help heal the world and make it a better place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to spend 10 dollars</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2011-02-11-how-to-spend-10-dollars/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2011 10:03:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2011-02-11-how-to-spend-10-dollars/</guid>
      <description>Last month in my Illinois Jaycees newsletter article I talked about what you could do with 10 dollars and the Nothing But Nets Program. How cool is this, today I came across a you tube video asking the same question. The point of the matter is for 10 dollars you can save a person from malaria. Get involved in the Nothing But Nets campaign it can prevent the spread of a disease.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Top Ten WordPress Plugins</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2011-01-29-my-top-ten-wordpress-plugins/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jan 2011 17:59:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2011-01-29-my-top-ten-wordpress-plugins/</guid>
      <description>Hey so I thought it was time to put out another top ten list and what better topic then WordPress !!!!
Akismet The best dam comment spam filter out there. Simple Social – Sharing Widgets &amp;amp; Icons This is a great little plug in it allows you simple integration with basically any social network out there. kPicasa Gallery I found this plugin last month it makes it easy to integration a Picasa album into your website quickly Advanced Category Excluder OMG this is one of my favorite it allows you filter out post from your homepage or archives by category or tag.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Making Our Impact with Nothing But Net</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2011-01-24-making-our-impact-with-nothing-but-net/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2011 11:14:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2011-01-24-making-our-impact-with-nothing-but-net/</guid>
      <description>What can you do with 10 dollars? Hmmm buy a shirt, buy 2 footlong subs at subway, buy a couple gallons of gas, 2 cups of Grande coffee at starbucks, or save a life. Yup it’s true for just 10 dollars you can save a life. Malaria infects nearly 500 million people each year and kills more than one million of those who become infected. Last year State Chairwomen Sue Warmuskerken introduced us to the JCI Nothing But Nets program and with yours along with all the members of JCI efforts we have made an impact on this disease.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Allow For Me To Reintroduce Myself</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2011-01-24-allow-for-me-to-reintroduce-myself/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2011 09:45:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2011-01-24-allow-for-me-to-reintroduce-myself/</guid>
      <description>This year I’ll be serving as the Illinois Jaycees 2011 National Programs / Government Involvement State Chairmen or NPGI State Chair for short also I’ll be serving as the North Region Treasurer oh and also the Website Program Manager for the US Jaycees once again. The goal this year is promote the programs The US Jaycees and JCI have established to all of our chapters across the state. The Jaycees have a have long history of bring fourth change throughout the nation with programs like Get Out to Vote and other Government Involvement programs, Outstanding Young Farmers, Support Our Troops, Distinguish Service Award which became the Ten Outstanding Young Americans, Relay for life and just added in 2009 Riley’s Toys.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Support Camp New Hope</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2011-01-12-support-camp-new-hope/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2011 11:55:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2011-01-12-support-camp-new-hope/</guid>
      <description>Each year members of the Illinois Jaycees support Camp New Hope through various community drives and as part of our annual fund raising campaign. Camp New Hope Respite building started construction 10 years ago, but due to the loss of State and Federal funding and the despair of our current economy, the construction remains unfinished. This building is used for the year round respite program which gives reprive to those families with members with special needs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>T-SQL Tuesday 13: Interacting With The Business</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/sql/interacting-with-the-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/sql/interacting-with-the-business/</guid>
      <description>I come from a different world in my company, I’m not IT though I have formal training, I speak the lingo, and wear the uniform of Jeans, t-shirt, glasses and ton’s of geekieness in my swagger. I’m what they call Business Intelligence or better known as Shadow IT. Though i&amp;rsquo;m up front about what we do and the impact it has. In my company I’m the middle person between what the business thinks it wants and what it really needs long term.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introducing The New Mount Prospect Jaycees Website</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2010-12-10-introducing-the-new-mount-prospect-jaycees-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2010 15:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2010-12-10-introducing-the-new-mount-prospect-jaycees-website/</guid>
      <description>When the Mount Prospect Jaycees needed a update to their aging website which i first built back in 2008. I worked with the chapter executive board to bring a fresh new look to their website. For this site it required moving over all the current chapter contain as well as introducing some new features. I choose WordPress as the platform to host their site because two of their board members were familiar with it and training the rest of the board wouldn’t be a problem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grooving to the beats with Grooveshark</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2010-12-10-grooving-to-the-beats-with-grooveshark/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2010 10:41:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2010-12-10-grooving-to-the-beats-with-grooveshark/</guid>
      <description>So only my old AIM friends would get that title. But just last week grooveshark.com went through a full revamp of their website, switching from a flash based website to the new internet language of html5. Which seems to quickly becoming the standard. I’m excited about the switch for two reasons. First technically you can you use the site now on your iPad and iPhone in the near future. I’ve tried it on my iPad the other night and i got a notice saying my computer was not running flash and asked if i want to continue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Things to make my life easier</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2010-11-30-things-to-make-my-life-easier/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2010 15:23:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2010-11-30-things-to-make-my-life-easier/</guid>
      <description>I thought it was time to put together a little list of my favorite computer things i use to make my life easier. No big deal just the things i use everyday no matter if I’m at work or at home. I find myself using these products all the time.
Hope you enjoy my list and post comments and share your thoughts
1) Evernote – I first found the app for my the iPad before i knew about the website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using DateDiff to Control Content</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/sql/using-datediff-to-control-content/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/sql/using-datediff-to-control-content/</guid>
      <description>Last Friday I got a data request from a group asking for a report to be generated bi-hourly for customer request that were not responded to in a time span of two hours. So looking at the data I noticed that there were two columns that were time stamped one when the request was submitted and another when the request was completed, so this was easy I filtered out where the completed data was null and wrote a where statement using a Datediff syntax to breakdown the input date time stamp by hour and then subtracting two so my sql statement looks like the following example.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Favorite Business Intelligence Blogs</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/sql/favorite-business-intelligence-blogs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/sql/favorite-business-intelligence-blogs/</guid>
      <description>As I start to dive deeper into the Business Intelligence area I&amp;rsquo;ve started putting together a list of my favorite blogs covering this area, in no particular order.
http://www.bidn.com/ http://sqlbi.blogspot.com/ http://cwebbbi.spaces.live.com/ http://denglishbi.spaces.live.com/ http://bi-polar23.blogspot.com/ http://sqlserverbiblog.com/ http://shahfaisalmuhammed.wordpress.com/ http://tomislavpiasevoli.spaces.live.com/default.aspx http://bimatters.spaces.live.com/ </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SSIS Reference Points</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/sql/ssis-reference-points/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/sql/ssis-reference-points/</guid>
      <description>This is a shout out to my former team member learning about SSIS packages for the first time and getting ready to move from SQL 2000 to SQL 2008. Here’s some good reference points for how to do the basics. Now before you call me and ask what does SSIS stands it stands for SQL Server Integration Services. So below is a couple links that i found i think you may find helpful in your new adventure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Virtual Meetings For Free</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2010-09-30-virtual-meetings-for-free/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2010 17:20:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2010-09-30-virtual-meetings-for-free/</guid>
      <description>You every want to plan a project or host a committee meeting virtually but don’t have a conference call number of your own or know where to start? Well your in luck thanks to a little company called Dimdim you can now host online meetings, trainings, and brainstorming sessions from the comfort of your own home for free. Dimdim is a software company that provides a web-based platform for real-time, rich-media collaboration and meetings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Documenting Isn’t That Hard</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2010-09-30-documenting-isnt-that-hard/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2010 16:52:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2010-09-30-documenting-isnt-that-hard/</guid>
      <description>Just like the title said it’s not that hard and it one of the most important things in software and process development is the the Documentation part. But it’s most often the most over looked do to time and no short term benefit. But long term after the developer has forgotten what they did back then the documentation they have written will still be there for the next developer to come along and revise, enhance, or just get a better understanding of what is taking place and how it done.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitter &amp; The North Region Jaycees</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2010-08-23-twitter-the-north-region-jaycees/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2010 08:20:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2010-08-23-twitter-the-north-region-jaycees/</guid>
      <description>What are you doing? that’s a question that you are probably asked dozens of time a day. How many of you use the Facebook status function each day? How many of you use it more than once each day? Well, this year the North Region Jaycees are trying something new and we will be using a free service named Twitter to communicate all kinds of one line answers, event postings, random thoughts, and newsflashes about articles recently added to the Region’s website www.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stupid Duplicates</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/sql/stupid-duplicates/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jul 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/sql/stupid-duplicates/</guid>
      <description>So the other day my former team member call me asking for help. She had inserted the same data into a table three or more times and needed to get rid of them. For those of you with duplications and need to delete them here’s a little statement i came up with and gave her.
DELETE FROM TBL_Employees
WHERE (EmpID IN
(SELECT MAX(EmpID) AS Expr2
FROM TBL_Employees
GROUP BY FirstName</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10 degrees in 365 days</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2010-06-19-10-degrees-in-365-days/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jun 2010 07:59:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2010-06-19-10-degrees-in-365-days/</guid>
      <description>Each year being in the Jaycees brings something exciting to do and well 2010 is no different. This year in addition to serving on my state’s board and the US Jaycees board I’ve decided to create my own personal challenge for myself. That is to be come a tenth degree Jaycee in the course of the year. The degree program is designed to build great leaders. It starts off at with the basics getting a person socially involved to develop the social and networking skills and then progress over time to the point of where the person is heading up committees, chapter, districts, and states.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Determing SQL Server Table Size Tip</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/sql/determing-sql-server-table-size-tip/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/sql/determing-sql-server-table-size-tip/</guid>
      <description>From time to time i run into problems of where some new table appears on m server and starts eating up all my space. Well i came across this blog posting a while back that does a great job of explaining how to determine the table sizes in a database in SQL 2000 it works in 2005 too. check it out and let me know what you think. http://www.mitchelsellers.com/blogs/articletype/articleview/articleid/121/determing-sql-server-table-size.aspx</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SQL Saturday 31 Wrapup</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/sql/sql-saturday-31-wrapup/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/sql/sql-saturday-31-wrapup/</guid>
      <description>Earlier this month i attended my first SQL meetup called SQL Saturday #31 i&amp;rsquo;m not sure why it&amp;rsquo;s numbered 31 cause i realized they don&amp;rsquo;t go in order. But yeah so it was hosted in Elk Grove so it wasn&amp;rsquo;t to far away. I knew it was going to be a awesome day when i met this guy in the registration line who reads my site and learned a couple SQL tricks from it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Date Formatting In SQL</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/sql/date-formatting-in-sql/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/sql/date-formatting-in-sql/</guid>
      <description>I got a request for a report the other day so I built this massive 90 line SQL statement to pull all the data requested. So I sent off a copy of the data report and the guy tells me that he needs the date formatted (YYYYMMDD) instead of (YYYY-MM-DD-HHMMSS) and then he was like is that going to be a problem and I was like ha not really. Give me a moment and I&amp;rsquo;ll send you a simple.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 2nd Online Training Announced</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2010-03-09-the-2nd-online-training-announced/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2010 08:53:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2010-03-09-the-2nd-online-training-announced/</guid>
      <description>The next online training will be on Monday the 15th. We will be learning about how to make on online survey and taking a look at three products in the market all of which are free. We will also learn how to build a survey using the Google Docs platform. Training is open to the first 50 people with 33 seats allocated to the state staff. Sign up for the training using the widget on the right side.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introducing The New Hoffman Estates Jaycees Website</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2010-02-28-introducing-the-new-hoffman-estates-jaycees-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2010 07:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2010-02-28-introducing-the-new-hoffman-estates-jaycees-website/</guid>
      <description>When the Hoffman Estates Jaycees needed a update to their aging website. I worked with the chapter executive board to bring a fresh new look to their website. For this site it required moving over all the current chapter contain as well as introducing some new features. I choose WordPress as the platform to host their site because two of their board members were familiar with it and training the rest of the board wouldn’t be a problem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Network Integration</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2010-02-12-social-network-integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2010 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2010-02-12-social-network-integration/</guid>
      <description>Integrating into social networks is just important as being on them in the past the US Jaycees website hasn’t made reference to our involvement with the online social networks. Today I introduced a new module called stalker which allows us to promote our social network pages on our homepage as well as I wrote a custom module for displaying the organizations Facebook fan page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Business As Usual</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2010-02-02-business-as-usual/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2010 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2010-02-02-business-as-usual/</guid>
      <description>Today I’ll begin working the US Jaycees Site. My first task is to perform a Full DB backup just incase something goes wrong. This was going well until I ran into my first problem i was unable to access the db server which is no big deal since i could get into the php admin panel. It’s been so long since I’ve had to perform a manual backup in MYSQL. But that what they make Google for right?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guess Who Updating the site</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2010-01-29-guess-who-updating-the-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2010 08:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2010-01-29-guess-who-updating-the-site/</guid>
      <description>It’s me !!!!!it was just recently announced that I’ll be taking the US Jaycees website from the current webmaster David. No real reason why was giving why the change. But they posted they were looking on the site and I responded with a letter to President Jeff and the Exec board. Look for more postings over the 12 months about my adventures as their 2010 Website Program Manager.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Fav 5 Windows Home Server Add-ins</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2009-11-12-my-fav-5-windows-home-server-add-ins/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2009 07:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2009-11-12-my-fav-5-windows-home-server-add-ins/</guid>
      <description>The other day I was talking with a friend about my Windows Home Server configuration and thought I would post a little something about what addins I’m running or as the the title said my Fav 5. I like to keep my WHS running light and simple so the addins I like to use take advantage of features already built into windows 2003 and don’t put any extra strain on the server.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The day after the 120 days are up</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2009-11-01-the-day-after-the-120-days-are-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2009 09:29:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2009-11-01-the-day-after-the-120-days-are-up/</guid>
      <description>First let me start by saying Microsoft allows you to download any of there new operating systems for trial period usually 120 days but some are 90. My 120 day trial period for windows home server ended on September 15th. I waited all the way to 121st day to upgrade even though I knew by the 90th day I was planning on buying it. So when I finally got around to getting a licensed copy, which I actually ended up getting it for my birthday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sox Pride !!!!</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2009-09-07-sox-pride/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2009 13:52:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2009-09-07-sox-pride/</guid>
      <description>So as the 2009 season wraps up unhopeful unless a major blessing happens, today I started playing with the photo collage feature on Picasa 3 and I thought I would put together a White Sox one from all my photos over years with family and friends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The First 5 Things I do When I Get a New BlackBerry</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2009-08-17-the-first-5-things-i-do-when-i-get-a-new-blackberry/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2009 16:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2009-08-17-the-first-5-things-i-do-when-i-get-a-new-blackberry/</guid>
      <description>Last week i got the new Blackberry 8520 Curve and i though I would write my first five things similar to ones did on the blackberry blog site. Since i this my third blackberry I’ve got my steps setting up down pretty good.
Download Google Mobile Apps; OMG this has got to be my used applications on my blackberry. First the Google sync is one hell of an application it syncs up my address book and calendar to my Gmail account.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why i tweet</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2009-05-08-why-i-tweet/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2009 12:11:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2009-05-08-why-i-tweet/</guid>
      <description>I’m a really big fan of micro-Blog services for a couple reasons one I hate writing long blog postings and the other is just the simplicity of the technology I can just post to it with one hand while driving or while eating, or sitting in a meeting. Since I begin twittering just about three months ago I’ve posted over 600 updates. Everything from my daily status to just random questions, but hey so check out my stats below of my usage patterns.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Changing the default My documents</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2009-04-13-changing-the-default-my-documents/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2009 13:05:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2009-04-13-changing-the-default-my-documents/</guid>
      <description>I’m one of those weird people who use multiple computers each day to get work things done. When I’m in the office I use my desktop PC and then at home I use my work laptop, prior to last year accessing my work files on my Desktop from work was nearly impossible. An then everyone got their own personal network share about year. Since then I’ve been saving all my files to my share and accessing them their over our corp.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I Relay 4 Life</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2009-04-11-why-i-relay-4-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Apr 2009 18:21:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2009-04-11-why-i-relay-4-life/</guid>
      <description>My primary reason for support relay for life is as you may or may not know I lost my grand father to his battle with cancer a few years back and followed by two aunts a few months later. That made really think about cancer and we can cure it. Cancer is one of those diseases that effects people no matter if their rich or poor . If their Black or white, we all know someone who has been impacted by cancer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spring Consolidation</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2009-04-11-spring-consolidation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Apr 2009 14:15:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2009-04-11-spring-consolidation/</guid>
      <description>Ahh it’s the most wonderful time of the year, the sun is shining the grass is growing nice and green. It couldn’t be more picture perfect. I’m just relaxing at home outside with a miller lite and my laptop. I figure today was a great day to spend a little time cleaning up my network. My home is scanning for duplicate files across my network and when it’s done it will be time to dump some of those too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to find duplicate rows in SQL Server</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/sql/how-to-find-duplicate-rows-in-sql-server/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/sql/how-to-find-duplicate-rows-in-sql-server/</guid>
      <description>I ran into this problem the other day at work with duplicate rows while trying to merge data from two separate tables into the same table. I couldn&amp;rsquo;t remember so I just ran a quick search using Google and came across the solution on a Microsoft knowledge base page.
col1 col2
1 1 2</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Birthday Gogorichie.com</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2005-07-03-14127/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2005 20:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2005-07-03-14127/</guid>
      <description>On July 9th 2002 Gogorichie.com was born. Here are some stats recorded during the last year.
3,318 unique visitors came to the site, as determined by typical behavior of browsers with a non-rotating IP address and including a projection of the true number of visitors with rotating IP addresses.
The web site received 5,693 visits. A typical visitor examined 17.19 distinct files before leaving the site. A typical visit lasted for 6.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
