<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Richard Lewis</title>
    <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Richard Lewis</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 08:08:56 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://www.gogorichie.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>My Favorite VSCode Plugins Of 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/2025_fav_vscode_plugins/2025_fav_vscode_plugins/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 08:08:56 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/2025_fav_vscode_plugins/2025_fav_vscode_plugins/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://gogorichiesitefiles.blob.core.windows.net/publicfiles/Yonce.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Yonce Theme&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Back in 2019 I wrote a post about my favorite &lt;a href=&#34;https://code.visualstudio.com/&#34;&gt;VS Code&lt;/a&gt; plugins and here we are in 2025 and I’m still using it every single day. At this point VS Code has become my main IDE for both work and home projects. I still run Visual Studio from time to time, but VS Code has really become the Swiss Army knife for just about everything i run it for work task and home side projects and if i&amp;rsquo;m traveling i run it on my iPad via &lt;a href=&#34;https://vscode.dev/&#34;&gt;vscode.dev&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why I Left WordPress (And Never Looked Back)</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/so-long-wordpress/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 08:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/so-long-wordpress/</guid>
      <description>&lt;img src=&#34;https://gogorichiesitefiles.blob.core.windows.net/publicfiles/trashing_wp.png&#34; alt=&#34;WordPress&#34; style=&#34;width:50%; display:block; margin:auto;&#34; /&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Back in college on July 9th, 2002, I registered &lt;em&gt;gogorichie.com&lt;/em&gt; through GoDaddy. It was a spur-of-the-moment decision, driven by the curiosity of owning my own slice of the internet. Little did I know that domain would become my digital home for decades of blogging, experimentation, and tech journaling.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;the-breakup-with-wordpress&#34;&gt;The Breakup With WordPress&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;From LiveJournal to Blogspot and eventually to a self-hosted WordPress install in 2011, my blog has lived many lives. WordPress gave me ultimate flexibility. I could mold my blog into anything I wanted thanks to its massive plugin ecosystem. Over the years, I posted nearly 3000 blog entries — trust me, a lot of it was garbage — but it was mine, and I loved that freedom.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How I Automated Meeting Presence for My Family</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/office-meeting-indicator/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2025 08:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/office-meeting-indicator/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div style=&#34;display: flex; justify-content: center; gap: 2rem;&#34;&gt;&#xD;&#xA;    &lt;img src=&#34;https://gogorichiesitefiles.blob.core.windows.net/publicfiles/osf/ESP_Home_logo3.svg&#34; alt=&#34;ESPHome&#34; style=&#34;width: 200px;&#34;/&gt;&#xD;&#xA;    &lt;img src=&#34;https://gogorichiesitefiles.blob.core.windows.net/publicfiles/osf/home-assistant-wordmark-monochrome-on-light.png&#34; alt=&#34;Home Assistant&#34; style=&#34;width: 200px;&#34;/&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;br/&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Like many folks post-2020, I’ve been working from home a lot more, and with that came a new set of challenges — one of them being how to let my family know when I’m in a meeting without yelling across the house or hanging a note on the door. I decided to solve that problem the way any tech nerd would — with a bit of home automation magic.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Git vs Azure DevOps vs GitHub: Understanding the Differences</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/gitvsghvsado/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/gitvsghvsado/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;From time to time, I see folks confusing the products of &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com&#34;&gt;GitHub&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/devops/user-guide/what-is-azure-devops?view=azure-devops&#34;&gt;Azure DevOps&lt;/a&gt; with the version control of &lt;a href=&#34;https://git-scm.com/&#34;&gt;Git&lt;/a&gt; and the practices of &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ibm.com/think/topics/devops&#34;&gt;DevOps&lt;/a&gt;. In this post, I will break down terms like Git, GitHub, Azure DevOps, and DevOps to help clarify what each one does, their relationship with one another, and how they contribute to the software development lifecycle.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;1-git-version-control-system-vcs&#34;&gt;1. Git: Version Control System (VCS)&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://git-scm.com/&#34;&gt;Git&lt;/a&gt; is a distributed version control system created by Linus Torvalds in 2005 and actually it turns 20 this month. It helps developers track changes in their codebase, collaborate with team members, and manage different versions of a project efficiently.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How I Stream My Church Service to YouTube and Facebook</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/church_live_stream/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/church_live_stream/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How I Stream My Church Service to YouTube and Facebook — A Small Way to Give Back&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When the pandemic hit, a lot of things changed — including how we worship together. Suddenly, gathering in person wasn’t an option, and our church needed a way to stay connected. I knew I could help. Before all this, I worked as a developer advocate, so I’ve always enjoyed solving tech problems and sharing solutions. This time, I felt it was a chance to use that talent to serve God and my church community.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why You Should Attend DevOpsDays Chicago 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/devopsdayschicago2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 07:24:08 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/devopsdayschicago2025/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;If you’re a developer, DevOps Engineer, Operations Engineer, SRE, or anyone passionate about improving collaboration in tech, then &lt;a href=&#34;https://devopsdays.org/events/2025-chicago/welcome/&#34;&gt;DevOpsDays Chicago 2025&lt;/a&gt; is the conference you don’t want to miss. Having attended DevOpsDays in 2018, 2019, 2021, 2022, and 2023 and even speaking in 2022 I can confidently say that this event is one of the best opportunities to grow your skills, connect with peers, and stay ahead of industry trends.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The DevOpsDays Experience&#xA;DevOpsDays is not your typical tech conference. It blends expert-led talks with interactive Open Spaces that encourage deep discussions and real-world problem-solving. Unlike conferences that feel like one-way information dumps, DevOpsDays fosters a genuine community atmosphere where everyone’s voice matters. It’s a mix of structured learning, networking, and freeform discussions that you won’t find at many other industry events.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Office Meeting Indicator Version 2</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/office-meeting-indicator-v2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2024 07:24:08 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/office-meeting-indicator-v2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://gogorichiesitefiles.blob.core.windows.net/publicfiles/esp32-s3-matrix-5.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ESP32 S3 Matrix 8x8 64 LED&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Previously, I made a YouTube video demonstrating how to automate the detection of whether a meeting is happening using Home Assistant and a light. In that video, I used an ESP32 board and LED light strips controlled by WLED, integrated with Home Assistant for the automation. Since then, I’ve discovered the &lt;a href=&#34;https://amzn.to/3CPVFLV&#34;&gt;ESP32-S3 Matrix&lt;/a&gt; a compact and versatile development board featuring an ESP32-S3 processor and an 8x8 RGB LED matrix with 64 integrated LEDs. This board is perfect for creating interactive lighting projects, digital art, and real-time visual displays. Its compact design makes it ideal for my setup: a small device placed inside a wine press located outside my office to signal my current meeting status with lights.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My 2024 Network Rack Tour</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/my-2024-network-rack-tour/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 16:27:02 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/my-2024-network-rack-tour/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In my latest video, I’m giving you an exclusive tour of my &lt;strong&gt;2024 Home Network Rack&lt;/strong&gt;, showcasing the meticulously designed infrastructure that keeps our digital world running smoothly. From blazing-fast internet speeds to seamless multimedia streaming, this setup is all about performance, reliability, and cutting-edge tech.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;whats-inside-the-rack&#34;&gt;What’s Inside the Rack?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ubiquiti Products&lt;/strong&gt;: Experience unparalleled internet speeds and rock-solid connectivity powered by some of the best networking gear on the market.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Home Server Magic&lt;/strong&gt;: Discover how I manage streaming, file storage, and automation with my home server running [software of choice]. It’s the unsung hero of our entertainment and productivity ecosystem.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Smart Home Integration&lt;/strong&gt;: See how the rack ties into our smart devices, creating a seamless and efficient living experience.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This rack isn’t just tech—it’s the backbone of our modern lifestyle.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My 2024 Unraid Server Setup</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/my-2024-unraid-server/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 06:27:02 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/my-2024-unraid-server/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I’m thrilled to share my latest YouTube video showcasing my 2024 Unraid server setup! In just 10 minutes, I walk you through how I use the power of Unraid to create the ultimate centralized platform for all my digital needs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here’s what I cover in the video:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;🎵 Music – How I organize and access my entire collection.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;📸 Photos – Keeping precious memories safe and easy to browse.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;🎥 Movies – Streaming my favorite films seamlessly.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;📁 Files – Effortlessly managing all my important data.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;🐳 Docker Containers – Running powerful apps and tools with ease.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;💻 Virtual Machines – Hosting multiple VMs for work and play.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a seasoned Unraid user or just exploring the possibilities, this video is packed with tips and insights to help you unlock the full potential of your server.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Enable GitHub Copilot Within Your Organization</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/githubcopilot-enabling/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2023 06:27:02 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/githubcopilot-enabling/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This blog post was written for future Richard and anyone else who might be looking for documentation on where to start with enabling GitHub Copilot within an organization. The process is pretty simple but might be diffcult to find where to start.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is GitHub Copilot?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;GitHub Copilot is an AI-powered autocomplete tool that acts as a peer programmer, assisting in writing code. if you want to dive deeper into Copilot you can find more information about GitHub Copilot on the &lt;a href=&#34;https://resources.github.com/copilot-for-business/?ef_id=_k_e65e07530d46189e67c96210e860b6be_k_&amp;amp;OCID=AIDcmmc3fhtaow_SEM__k_e65e07530d46189e67c96210e860b6be_k_&amp;amp;msclkid=e65e07530d46189e67c96210e860b6be&#34;&gt;github resource&lt;/a&gt; site.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Azure Stream Analytics Overview</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/azure-stream-analytics-overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 08:08:56 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/azure-stream-analytics-overview/</guid>
      <description>&lt;table&gt;&#xA;  &lt;thead&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;th style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://gogorichiesitefiles.blob.core.windows.net/publicfiles/WebAppStream.jpeg&#34; alt=&#34;Stream Analytics&#34;&gt;&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/thead&gt;&#xA;  &lt;tbody&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Simple design of realtime streaming from Application Insights to PowerBI&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/tbody&gt;&#xA;&lt;/table&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I recently dived into the exciting world of Azure Stream Analytics If you&amp;rsquo;re scratching your head and wondering what the heck that is, don&amp;rsquo;t worry - I&amp;rsquo;ve got you covered.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Simply put, Azure Stream Analytics is a cloud-based service that lets you analyze data in real-time as it&amp;rsquo;s being streamed in from various sources. Think of it as your personal data magician that can extract insights from your data as soon as it hits the cloud. With Stream Analytics, you can analyze everything from IoT device data to social media posts and beyond.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Home Automation Observability With Terraform and Grafana</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/homeautomationobservability/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/homeautomationobservability/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://gogorichiesitefiles.blob.core.windows.net/publicfiles/tgi-image.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Image&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Being a DevOps and SRE minded person professionally has a big benefit when it comes to home automation. Im constantly looking for ways to make my home automation more efficient and easier to manage. One of the important things to consider in your home automation is observability this usually comes via a some sort of Dashboard usually this is an application or two you use to interact with your smart devices. But as your ecosystem grows and more devices are brought online you need a way to see the full landscape at once. To achieve this I use a combination of Docker Containers running Grafana and InfluxDB.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recommended DevOps Books</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/recommendeddevopsbooks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 20:36:01 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/recommendeddevopsbooks/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As a seasoned DevOps professional, I’m often asked to recommend resources for newcomers to understand the core principles and best practices of this field. Over the years, I’ve read many excellent books on DevOps, but these five stand out as essential reads for anyone looking to gain a solid, comprehensive understanding of DevOps.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://gogorichiesitefiles.blob.core.windows.net/publicfiles/books/Accelerate.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Accelerate&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The first I recommend is &lt;strong&gt;Accelerate&lt;/strong&gt; by Nicole Forsgren, Jez Humble, and Gene Kim. This is a must-read for anyone interested in software development and delivery. The book is based on extensive research about what drives high-performing teams and how to optimize software delivery practices. It offers practical advice and real-world examples to help organizations improve capabilities such as continuous delivery, monitoring, and experimentation. The authors provide a valuable roadmap for building a culture of continuous improvement.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://amzn.to/3IczzmK&#34;&gt;Amazon link&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Devops Days Nashville 2023 Recap</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/devopsdaysnashville2023recap/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 07:24:08 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/devopsdaysnashville2023recap/</guid>
      <description>&lt;table&gt;&#xA;  &lt;thead&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;th style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://gogorichiesitefiles.blob.core.windows.net/publicfiles/dod/dod-nash-speaker.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Conference Speakers&#34;&gt;&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/thead&gt;&#xA;  &lt;tbody&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;2023 DevOps Conference Speakers&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/tbody&gt;&#xA;&lt;/table&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I recently attended the &lt;a href=&#34;https://devopsdays.org/events/2023-nashville/welcome/&#34;&gt;2023 DevOps Days Nashville&lt;/a&gt; conference in Tennessee, and it was an incredible experience. As with all DevOps Days conferences, the themes and speakers were decided by the local organizers, which made for a unique and diverse range of sessions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;On the first day of the conference, I attended some fantastic sessions that provided some great ideas that I can use with my clients. I particularly enjoyed the sessions on &amp;ldquo;How to launch a lifesaving platform,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Converting the Automation Resistant,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Stop Committing Your Secrets - Git Hooks To The Rescue!&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Volunteering Your Skills with GeekCause.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Azure Static Web Apps: The Cloud&#39;s New Electric Vehicle</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/azurespringcleaning2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 22:00:56 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/azurespringcleaning2023/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://gogorichiesitefiles.blob.core.windows.net/publicfiles/asc23.png&#34; alt=&#34;Image&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Live Recording&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;See the following youtube video for a live demo recording of my talk.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;&#xA;      &lt;iframe allow=&#34;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share; fullscreen&#34; loading=&#34;eager&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;strict-origin-when-cross-origin&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/mH3XxWU_vfI?autoplay=0&amp;amp;controls=1&amp;amp;end=0&amp;amp;loop=0&amp;amp;mute=0&amp;amp;start=0&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; title=&#34;YouTube video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Overview&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Welcome to day one of &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.azurespringclean.com/&#34;&gt;Azure Spring Cleaning 2023!&lt;/a&gt;. Azure Static Web Apps have been generally available for about one and a half years now, and I&amp;rsquo;ve been excited about this service since day one. Professionally, I help customers reduce software delivery complexity, so for me, Static Web Apps are an amazing idea that reduces the time needed to get services up and running.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Azure Synapse Overview</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/azure-synapse-overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 08:46:19 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/azure-synapse-overview/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://gogorichiesitefiles.blob.core.windows.net/publicfiles/synapse-swag-2022.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Image&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Earlier this year I joined the &lt;a href=&#34;https://azure.github.io/Synapse/influencers/&#34;&gt;Azure Synapse Influencer Program&lt;/a&gt;. But I don&amp;rsquo;t receive payments as an influencer instead I get a wide range of benefits, such as early access to new features and capabilities, access to exclusive training and resources, and opportunities to engage with the Azure Synapse product team and also the occasional free swag like a coffee cup and sticker. I joined the program to build my knowledge around the platform and be able to show its value of it to my clients.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Devops Days Tampa Bay 2022 Recap</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/devopsdaystampabay2022recap/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 07:24:08 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/devopsdaystampabay2022recap/</guid>
      <description>&lt;table&gt;&#xA;  &lt;thead&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;th style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://pbs.twimg.com/media/FfmtUiPXkAMFOTl?format=jpg&amp;amp;name=medium&#34; alt=&#34;Richard Presenting&#34;&gt;&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/thead&gt;&#xA;  &lt;tbody&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Richard Presenting LMAO Helps During Outages&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/tbody&gt;&#xA;&lt;/table&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In 2022, I had a fantastic year of reconnecting with my passions, meeting new individuals, delivering presentations, and gaining knowledge from experienced professionals. To conclude my travels and speaking engagements for the year, I had the privilege of journeying to Florida and delivering a talk at &lt;a href=&#34;https://devopsdays.org/events/2022-tampa/welcome/&#34;&gt;DevOps Days Tampa&lt;/a&gt;. Having attended DevOps conferences for many years, I was thrilled to create an engaging presentation that encouraged collaboration and prompted attendees to reflect on critical considerations when preparing for on-call duties.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Built International Session 4: The Truth about Black Consultants Speakers Panel</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/built-speakers-panel-appearance/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/built-speakers-panel-appearance/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://gogorichiesitefiles.blob.core.windows.net/publicfiles/Built0928event.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Event Flyer&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A few days ago the opportunity to joined a Blacks United In Leading Tech speakers panel event to discuss &amp;ldquo;The truth about Black Consultants&amp;rdquo;. This was my first event with this group, it was a great conversation we talked about our personal journeys in the industry of consulting while sharing valuable insights and advice around some key areas of interest:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Transferable skills for various positions in consulting.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;How to set the right expectations and key behaviors.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;How to find a job as a Black Consultant.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Best advice on how to break into this industry.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Blacks united in leading tech international is a great orginzation.Through community-focused activities, events and programs, BUILT International is part of the united movement, bringing equality in tech. You can find out more about them on their website &lt;a href=&#34;www.builtinternational.org&#34;&gt;builtinternational.org&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Devops Days Chicago 2022 Recap</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/devopsdayschicago2022recap/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 07:24:08 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/devopsdayschicago2022recap/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I had the opportunity to attend another &lt;a href=&#34;https://devopsdays.org/events/2022-chicago/welcome/&#34;&gt;DevOps Days Chicago&lt;/a&gt; which is a regional conference focused on software development, IT infrastructure operations, and the intersection between them called DevOps. This was the fourth DevOps days I have attended, third in person, and first as a speaker. Speaking of which it’s good to be able to get back to a conference in person. I’m an extrovert so I love meeting new people and don’t get that really from virtual conferences. You’ll learn a lot, but I missed that one part when I was a Developer Advocate at Coyote are used to attend a lot of conferences and user group meetings, and 2020 kind of put a stop to that in many ways. It was great to see people in person. People I hadn’t seen in a long time like from a company I left 2 years ago or from local user groups and find out what they’re up to now and how their life has changed over the last few years. It was great meeting new and future business partners and hearing from the vendors about what makes their products different than others. Heck even one &lt;a href=&#34;https://itnext.io/spice-up-your-infrastructure-as-code-with-tacos-1a9c179e0783&#34;&gt;TACO product vendors&lt;/a&gt; gave away 100 bucks cash for looking at and testing their product in a demo environment.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts On Azure Cache For Redis</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/thoughts-on-azure-cache-4-redis/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 08:46:19 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/thoughts-on-azure-cache-4-redis/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Recently I took some time to revisit Azure Cache for Redis I got first introduced to the service in 2018 and a lot has changed since then. I won’t go into detail about &lt;a href=&#34;https://redis.io/docs/about/&#34;&gt;Redis&lt;/a&gt; and what it is or What is &lt;a href=&#34;https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/resources/cloud-computing-dictionary/what-is-caching/#overview&#34;&gt;caching&lt;/a&gt;. But instead, I want to share my thoughts on using it on the Azure platform.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A particular use benefit of using Azure Cache for Redis instead of the self-hosting version for data cache needs is it will allow a business to bring the frequently called data to the cloud so that the data can be called faster with higher availability. This is perfect for situations where you have a frequently queried data source stored within a private network with high latency and an even higher constraint on memory usage from on-prem servers.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ubiquiti Unifi Setup Iteration Four</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/ubiquiti-unifi-setup-iteration-four/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 17:05:31 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/ubiquiti-unifi-setup-iteration-four/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Recap&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is a continuation of my 2020 network overhaul. You can read the details about how this project started at this &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/my-2020-ubiquiti-unifi-setup/&#34;&gt;link&lt;/a&gt;.  I ended the updates to my home network in 2020 in a good place and by that I mean everything was running smoothly with the full network being managed by software. There were no issues but lot’s of opportunities for improvement. So that left me thinking my 2021 improvements would be focused on reducing dependencies on 3rd party cloud services such as Ring and Google Nest cameras. Since everything was working just fine I was in no hurry to buy devices that were being sold with a markup. So I slowly began to acquire devices toward the end goal as devices went GA and deals popped up at Microcenter and eBay since this would be the most expensive part of the network.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taking My Security Grade From D to A</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/security-grade/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 20:21:20 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/security-grade/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://gogorichiesitefiles.blob.core.windows.net/publicfiles/a-cert.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Alt&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Backstory&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For my website, security has always been a second-class citizen I&amp;rsquo;ve never treated it fairly outside of the basic practices of an SSL certificate and patching of the host and any plugins I might be using. I had the opportunity to join Scott Hanselman for a small group session hosted by my company and one of the things he talked about was providing server-side security and sound of mind to users. He asked the audience for someone&amp;rsquo;s website address to show security vulnerabilities so I was quick to volunteer mine I assume my website was ok I knew that I was running a Hugo static hosted website on Netlify so I wasn’t truly concerned. He pulled up the website &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.securityheaders.com&#34;&gt;securityheaders.com&lt;/a&gt; and scanned gogorichie.com needless to say I was surprised my site ranked in as a D on a grading scale of A+ to R.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terrafy Knowledge Share</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/terrafyknowledge/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 22:46:02 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/terrafyknowledge/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A little disclaimer here, these are notes from a live demo on 4-28-22 sorry if this doesn&amp;rsquo;t make sense later.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Overview:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Azure Terrafy is a new tool currently in preview as of April 27th from Microsoft designed to help you export Azure Resources listed within the AzureRM provider to a terraform main.tf file and maintain a state file.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How To Install It:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To be able to install Terrafy you&amp;rsquo;ll need to download the binary from the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/Azure/aztfy&#34;&gt;github repo&lt;/a&gt;. If you haven&amp;rsquo;t installed terrform you&amp;rsquo;ll want to do that as well. &lt;a href=&#34;https://learn.hashicorp.com/tutorials/terraform/install-cli&#34;&gt;Click here for details&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DevOps Days Birmingham Alabama 2022 Talk</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/devopsdaysbham-2022-talk/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/devopsdaysbham-2022-talk/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Thanks for attending my talk on LMAO Helps During Outages at &lt;a href=&#34;https://devopsdays.org/events/2022-birmingham-al/welcome/&#34;&gt;DevOps Days Birmingham 2022&lt;/a&gt;. As promised in the talk i wanted to share my slides for all. For those who missed my talk but stumbled across this post. My talk was about solving the problem of when your company has an outage but there is no need to sweat just remember to LMAO and you’ll get through it having a combination of logs, metrics, alerts, and an observability tool in place will help your company LOL through it.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Professional Technical Interviewee Guest Appearance</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/professional-technical-interviewee-appearance/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/professional-technical-interviewee-appearance/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A few months back had the opportunity to joined my friend Taylor Dorsett on his Podcast to talk about Professional Technical Interviews from a DevOps perspective. If you&amp;rsquo;re interested in the DevOps space this is a great conversation to listen. Be sure to check it out over on his Youtube channel &lt;a href=&#34;https://youtu.be/t7QUvYqGS8s&#34;&gt;Professional Technical Interviewee with Taylor Dorsett&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;&#xA;      &lt;iframe allow=&#34;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share; fullscreen&#34; loading=&#34;eager&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;strict-origin-when-cross-origin&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/t7QUvYqGS8s?autoplay=0&amp;amp;controls=1&amp;amp;end=0&amp;amp;loop=0&amp;amp;mute=0&amp;amp;start=0&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; title=&#34;YouTube video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Notifications on Certificate Expiration Dates Using Azure Key Vault</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/keyvault-handlingsslcert/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2021 11:45:53 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/keyvault-handlingsslcert/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Back in July fellow Azure blogger &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/SCAutomation&#34;&gt;Billy York&lt;/a&gt; wrote a &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cloudsma.com/2021/07/monitor-ssl-cert-Azure-monitor/&#34;&gt;blog post&lt;/a&gt; about Monitoring SSL certificates with Azure monitor utilizing a standard test within App Insights, it&amp;rsquo;s really cool that Azure finally added this ability. I want to talk about an alternative less known method using Azure Key Vault certificate contacts and lifetime contacts.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is Azure Key Vault?&lt;/strong&gt;&#xA;&lt;img src=&#34;https://azure.microsoft.com/svghandler/key-vault/?width=600&amp;amp;height=315&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For those who are unfamiliar with The Azure service Azure Key Vault the fastest way to sum it up is that its a cloud service on Azure used for storing sensitive application information like tokens, passwords, API keys as well as TLS and SSL certificates used by resources on Azure or accessing Azure resources. The benefit of using a service like this is it will greatly reduce the risk of secrets being leaked accidentally. If you would like a more comprehensive overview of the service go to the &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/Azure/key-vault/general/&#34;&gt;Azure Key Vault website&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My 2020 Ubiquiti Unifi Setup</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/my-2020-ubiquiti-unifi-setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2021 23:05:31 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/my-2020-ubiquiti-unifi-setup/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve been using Ubiquiti products since late 2018 to improve the wireless experience of my wife in our townhouse. I came across the product line while trying to solve the problem of getting decent wire coverage across a 2500 Sq foot two-story townhouse. I tried mesh network products from Netgear, Google, and some other companies always with the same problem repeaters would fail, the handoff between access points was awful, and most importantly the quality of service was crap leaving my wife frustrated. After tons of YouTube videos and articles, I decided to go with the Ubiquiti Unifi product line with the long-term plan of upgrading my whole home network over two years to spread out the cost. The products aren&amp;rsquo;t cheap, they last long and they have a great resell value as far tech hardware goes.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hello World</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/hello_world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 22:49:37 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/hello_world/</guid>
      <description>First post using Hugo</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About Richard!</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2020 23:53:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;center&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;p align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;img src=&#34;https://gogorichiesitefiles.blob.core.windows.net/publicfiles/avataaars.png&#34;&#xD;&#xA;        alt=&#34;Picture&#34;&#xD;&#xA;        width=&#34;300&#34;&#xD;&#xA;        height=&#34;400&#34;&#xD;&#xA;        style=&#34;display: block; margin: 0 auto&#34; /&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;/center&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Richard is a highly skilled and experienced IT professional with over 20 years of experience in the industry. With a focus on process improvement through automation, he has expertise in the practice of DevOps, which involves delivering high-quality software through a combination of people, processes, and products. Throughout his career, Richard has worked with a wide range of IT organizations, from startups to Fortune 500 companies, and has learned from some of the best in the industry.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Favorite VSCode Plugins Of 2019</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/2019_fav_vscode_plugins/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2019 23:53:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/2019_fav_vscode_plugins/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;summary.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;SynthWave &amp;lsquo;84 theme&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;2019 was a big year for me using &lt;a href=&#34;https://code.visualstudio.com/&#34;&gt;VS Code&lt;/a&gt; before the beginning of the year I was still using &lt;a href=&#34;https://notepad-plus-plus.org&#34;&gt;Notepad++&lt;/a&gt; along with &lt;a href=&#34;https://visualstudio.microsoft.com&#34;&gt;Visual Studio&lt;/a&gt; as my daily IDE&amp;rsquo;s. But in January I tried to use VS Code every day for 30 days and I haven&amp;rsquo;t stopped and along the way, I also convinced a few of my Co-workers to convert over as well. I remember reading the &lt;a href=&#34;https://insights.stackoverflow.com/survey/2018/#development-environments-and-tools&#34;&gt;2018 Stack Overflow release their annual Developer survey results&lt;/a&gt; last December, one of the interesting things that I noticed was that VS Code had risen to the top as the Most Popular Development Environment among Developers and Admins with 35% of 75,398 respondents claiming to use it which is pretty cool for a tool-less than 5 years old. What makes VS Code so popular is first it&amp;rsquo;s platform agnostic, then the design is clean simple and how easy it is to create and add an extension to the &lt;a href=&#34;https://marketplace.visualstudio.com/vscode&#34;&gt;marketplace&lt;/a&gt;. That means depending on the type of task programming or administration you want to do at that time VS Code can help you accomplish it. Ok so here are some of my favorite plugins I use.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Code Nation: The Future Of Tomorrow</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/the-future-of-tomorrow/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2019 22:49:37 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/the-future-of-tomorrow/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Part my role at Coyote involves me work with community orginzations. In early 2019 Coyote&amp;rsquo;s Software Development group became involved with &lt;a href=&#34;https://codenation.org/&#34;&gt;Code Nation&lt;/a&gt;, an 501c3 organization based out of New York, which is focused on equipping students, in under-resourced high schools, with the skills, experiences, and connections that give them access to careers in technology.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Code Nation’s approach is using a volunteer teaching corp of hundreds of professional web and software&#xA;developers, that provide tuition-free coding courses and work-based learning programs to students of&#xA;these under-resourced schools. &lt;a href=&#34;https://codenation.org/&#34;&gt;Code Nation&lt;/a&gt; focuses on Latinx and Black students, 45% of these students being female.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Daily Grind Guest Appearance</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/daily-grind-interview/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/daily-grind-interview/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://www.kjfwi.org/index/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/DG-circle-logo-copy-297x300.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;KJ foundation logo&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Earlier this month I dropped by my friend Kelly Johnson&amp;rsquo;s podcast she is just starting up &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.kjfwi.org/the-daily-grind//&#34;&gt;The Daily Grind Podcast&lt;/a&gt; check out our conversation as we talk about Pickleball, Jaycees, Software Conferences, and what i do as a Developer Advocate.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;iframe src=&#34;https://anchor.fm/dailygrindpod/embed/episodes/Episode-4-Special-Guest-Richard-Lewis-e54l88/a-alra8d&#34; height=&#34;102px&#34; width=&#34;400px&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; scrolling=&#34;no&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://anchor.fm/dailygrindpod/episodes/Episode-4-Special-Guest-Richard-Lewis-e54l88&#34;&gt;Click here to subscribe&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What WordPress Plugins am I using in 2017?</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2017-11-01-what-wordpress-plugins-am-i-using/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2017 16:31:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2017-11-01-what-wordpress-plugins-am-i-using/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It’s been four years since I wrote my last update about what plugins I’m using on my WordPress platform. I’ve gotten more simple about the plugins and what I need them to do for me. Last time I wrote a post about the plugins their were seven and now I’m only running five.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div&gt;| Akismet Anti-Spam | By Automattic | This plugin helps you block and filter out spammer comments. According to them Akismet blocks 99.9% of spam from reaching your blog. I think they do a great job and I love it and I’ve been using it since 2010. |&#xD;&#xA;|---|---|---|&#xD;&#xA;| GoDaddy Pro Sites Worker | By GoDaddy | I manage quite a few Jaycee WordPress sites and this plugin is amazing it lets me manage the backups and updates on the backend all from one screen. It’s like OMS for WordPress on Godaddy . |&#xD;&#xA;| iThemes Security | By iThemes | This Plugin helps you lock down WordPress platform and is easy-to-use. |&#xD;&#xA;| Jetpack by WordPress.com | By Automattic | I mentioned this one last time. |&#xD;&#xA;| Redirection |  | Helps you manage all your 301 redirects and monitor 404 errors |&#xD;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why I Jaycee</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/jci/why_i_jaycee/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 15:43:51 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/jci/why_i_jaycee/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;iljc1.jpeg&#34; alt=&#34;Illinois Jaycees Member with IL Gov. Bruce Rauner &amp;amp; State Senator Charlie Meier&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The second week of October annually is Jaycee Week, it&amp;rsquo;s the week where we as Jaycees celebrate the founding of our organization in 1915 by Henry Giessenbier Jr. Ironically this month marks my 14th year as a member. So what better time of the year than now to share with you why I Jaycee? I joined the Jaycees to help make my community a better place. But I stay a Jaycee because it gives me the opportunity to be a Young Active Citizen, who can create positive change within my community. What&amp;rsquo;s the difference? Well making my community a better place is about helping my fellow-man or women with their need and creating positive change in my community is about fixing the root cause that is causing hardship to my fellow-man or women. This is one of the most important things the Jaycees have taught me and have given me the ability to do. Most of the time people tackle problems with a one-time donation or one day of volunteer work, but as Jaycees, we focus on making a sustainable impact.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Favorite Salesforce Tools</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2014-10-27-my-favorite-salesforce-tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2014 07:38:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2014-10-27-my-favorite-salesforce-tools/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;TextRun SCX228852166&#34; xml:lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;NormalTextRun SCX228852166&#34;&gt;Last year &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;TextRun SCX228852166&#34; xml:lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;NormalTextRun SCX228852166&#34;&gt;I&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;TextRun SCX228852166&#34; xml:lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;NormalTextRun SCX228852166&#34;&gt; came across a post by &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://agilecloudconsulting.blogspot.com/2013/11/my-favorite-free-sfdc-tools.html&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;TextRun Underlined SCX228852166&#34; xml:lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;NormalTextRun SCX228852166&#34;&gt;Sharif &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;TextRun Underlined SCX228852166&#34; xml:lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;NormalTextRun SCX228852166&#34;&gt;Shaalan&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;TextRun SCX228852166&#34; xml:lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;NormalTextRun SCX228852166&#34;&gt; on his blog &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://agilecloudconsulting.blogspot.com/2013/11/my-favorite-free-sfdc-tools.html&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;TextRun Underlined SCX228852166&#34; xml:lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;NormalTextRun SCX228852166&#34;&gt;Salesforce.com Tips, Tricks, Solutions, and Thoughts&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;TextRun SCX228852166&#34; xml:lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;NormalTextRun SCX228852166&#34;&gt; talking about his favorite Salesforce Tools he uses quite often and I really enjoyed his posting, so I thought I would share my favorite tools. Salesforce.com prides it’s self as a &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;TextRun SCX228852166&#34; xml:lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;NormalTextRun SCX228852166&#34;&gt;“No Software”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;TextRun SCX228852166&#34; xml:lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;NormalTextRun SCX228852166&#34;&gt; company meaning everything you need to get up and running is in the product and platform. Well you may not need software to get up and running on Salesforce but it takes great tools to keep to running smooth and efficient. This week I wanted to share with you my favorite tools that make my daily Salesforce administration and development easy. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Experience with Freedompop</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2014-08-20-my-experience-with-freedompop/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2014 18:56:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2014-08-20-my-experience-with-freedompop/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:#404040;font-family:Arial;font-size:12pt;&#34;&gt;I live outside of Chicago so there are a lot of options for mobile high speed internet. My cellular carrier is Sprint which has amazing LTE service and I’m getting on average 24Mbps down but there tethering plan is not worth the monthly cost for my usage. I first heard about Freedompop via a podcast called Tech News Today a couple of years ago so I started to get familiar with it back then but really didn’t have a need for it at the time. I would use mobile internet when I need too, which is mainly during commute to and from work to work while on the local rail service. I tried tethered to my phone in the beginning but founded it stupid to pay so much to use so little of my mobile data plan. I tried did from November until January and then I figured I would pick up a Freedompop online for a great deal. I was leery at first with the fact that runs on the Sprint WIMAX network which use to be owned by Clear Wireless but I figured let’s give it a ride and see it was a small investment oppose to keeping on paying Sprint. The cost of hardware was 25 bucks which included shipping, first month of service, what they call Freedompop premier, and 2GB of data for the plan. After that all that would cost me 20 bucks. But I figure I would cancel and drop down to the free plan of 500mb of data after the first month. The first thing that impressed with the quick time to delivery, I ordered my unit on a Monday afternoon and received it by Thursday via FedEx oppose to UPS Mail Innovation or UPS Sure post or some other hybrid with the USPS.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monitor Your Salesforce Instance Via An Automated Email</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2014-03-04-monitor-your-salesforce-instance-via-an-automated-email/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2014 15:29:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2014-03-04-monitor-your-salesforce-instance-via-an-automated-email/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.gogorichie.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/03/salesforce_logo-300x235.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.gogorichie.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/03/salesforce_logo-300x235.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;salesforce&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One of the challenges I face within Salesforce is noticing performance issues before my users do. It doesn’t happen to often but when it does my users notice. Like any other system Salesforce is only as weak as its weakest link. To help me stay ahead without constantly having to look at &lt;a href=&#34;https://trust.salesforce.com&#34;&gt;trust.salesforce.com&lt;/a&gt; I’ve created a zap using &lt;a href=&#34;http://zpr.io/gamt&#34;&gt;Zapier&lt;/a&gt; to monitor the rss feed for my server and send me a email when an incident is reported though the rss feed. Check out my zap below.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>T-SQL Tuesday 050: Automation, Get Work Done While Sleeping</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/sql/t-sql-tuesday-50/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/sql/t-sql-tuesday-50/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://gogorichiesitefiles.blob.core.windows.net/publicfiles/tsqltuesday.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;T-SQL Tusday&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s been a while since I&amp;rsquo;ve written a #&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/search?q=tsql2sday&amp;amp;src=typd&#34;&gt;tsql2sday&lt;/a&gt; post, but thought that this month&amp;rsquo;s topic was worthy of me hoping into the pool with the #sqlfamily. This month the subject is &amp;ldquo;Automation&amp;rdquo;. chosen by Hemanth D. (&lt;a href=&#34;http://sqlchow.wordpress.com/&#34;&gt;Blog&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/SqlChow&#34;&gt;@SqlChow&lt;/a&gt;). If you want to read the opening post, please click the image above. I&amp;rsquo;m lover of software automation and been a fan since writing my first macro in Excel when I was in high school. I loved anything that makes it easier for you to get more done with less. Back in the 2000&amp;rsquo;s I got introduced to SQL 2000 and DTS and it changed my world. My first package I created was awesome and so exciting it took data from database and put it into another one and then truncated the table, once I scheduled it to run I was able to not worry about handling that task anymore and sleep peacefully. Since then I&amp;rsquo;ve found my passion and made a living improving businesses through process improvement using automation.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Favorite Salesforce Blogs</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2013-12-12-my-favorite-salesforce-blogs/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2013 12:13:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2013-12-12-my-favorite-salesforce-blogs/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I love to learn and talk SQL all day everyday which gave me the inspiration for my blog post about my favorite &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.gogorichie.com/2010/10/ssis-reference-points/&#34;&gt;SSIS Reference Points&lt;/a&gt; and my &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.gogorichie.com/2010/10/bi-blogs/&#34;&gt;Favorite Business Intelligence Blogs&lt;/a&gt; in the past. So without further adieu I present to my list of what I blogs I commonly read in the Salesforce area and of course there in no particular order. I’ve built on the platform and written functions around it off and on over the last 4 years. So when I want to learn a little something something I check out these cool blogs they’re cross products and industries and all wholesome goodness.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>St. Judes &amp; Me</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2013-12-04-st-judes-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2013 10:06:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2013-12-04-st-judes-me/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Each I give my time and money to many causes. The way I handle giving my time and money to causes is simple. Through the Jaycees I’m able to give my time to many causes in the way of service to my local community and of course my favorite is Hospital Care-a-van which was run by the Mount Prospect Jaycees. Now as for money, each year I pick a different organization I’m interested in and give my money to them and I ask my friends to join in and support me in making an impact in that organizations cause. Last year I picked the United Nations Nothing But Nets organization which help prevents Malaria by providing bed nets around the world. This year I’ve chosen St. Judes Children’s Hospital. St. Jude Children’s Research Hospital is internationally recognized for its pioneering research and treatment of children with cancer and other catastrophic diseases. St. Jude is the first and only pediatric cancer center to be designated as a Comprehensive Cancer Center by the National Cancer Institute and we all know cancer sucks. St. Jude Children’s Research Hospital is internationally recognized for its pioneering research and treatment of children with cancer and other catastrophic diseases. You can help out by making a donation to&lt;a href=&#34;%20www.mystjudeevent.org/rlewis&#34;&gt; www.mystjudeevent.org/rlewis&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DreamForce 2013 Wrapup</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/dreamforce2013/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/dreamforce2013/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This year I made the trip to San Francisco for Salesforce&amp;rsquo;s annual DreamForce a five day conference that trumps all other conference.  Every aspect of the event was amazing and WOW 120,000 attendees.  The leadership speaker series, the trainings, the networking opportunities, and the parties were all great. My highlights and most memorable moments were getting to meet a couple of vendors that I only get to speak with on the phone including one who is located in France. But it wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be a good DreamForce without good entertainment and SalesForce raises the bar in this aspect as well the opening Keynote featured Huey Lewis and The News followed by an evening concert with GreenDay and Blonde. One after party I attended had MC Hammer DJing it. As well 100&amp;rsquo;s of parties across the city. So many parties that a marketing company crested Partyforce a app to track all the parties happening throughout the week. It&amp;rsquo;s even got checkin functions and leaderboard. The speaker lineup this year focused on women in technology (WIT) and Marc Benioff the CEO of Salesforce had two amazing speakers join him for on stage discussions on Tuesday he was joined by CEO Marissa Mayer of Yahoo their conversation lasted for about hour and a half and focus on changing the focus and culture at Yahoo.  It was very insightful and I took away from it a lot.  One thing she said that I&amp;rsquo;ll remember is how she has stays organized with a never ending priority list. The other thing that stuck with me was a comment she made regarding work life balance stating she lived her life a Vince Lombardi quote &amp;ldquo;His priority is God, family, Packers&amp;rdquo; or something like that. The next night Marc was joined on stage for a discussion with another amazing leader in the technology industry Sheryl Sandberg the CEO of Facebook.  Sheryl has recently released a new book called Lean In which all attendees received a free copy of.  In the book she talks about closing the gap on gender diversity. It was quite interesting conversation her and Marc had the take away from their fireside was being more conscious of my communication with female coworkers…..I guess. Over the next few weeks I&amp;rsquo;ll read her book Lean In and maybe I&amp;rsquo;ll rewrite a couple of post about it and my thoughts regarding. All my crazy pictures from the week long adventure can be seen at &lt;a href=&#34;https://plus.google.com/photos/105588147711118968857/albums/5951051845514062977?authkey=CM7cnL-j1I_GMw&#34;&gt;https://plus.google.com/photos/105588147711118968857/albums/5951051845514062977?authkey=CM7cnL-j1I_GMw&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spring Cleaning 2013</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2013-05-28-spring-cleaning/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2013 15:29:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2013-05-28-spring-cleaning/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.gogorichie.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/05/052813_2029_SpringClean1.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;It’s a couple of months since my last post and even longer since I’ve logged into the backend of my site. So this morning I did a lot admining of my site, kicked the morning off by removing a bunch of old plugins, old backups, and decided to take the twenty twelve theme for a test drive. While I’m at it’s been two years since my original posting on which &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.gogorichie.com/2011/01/my-top-ten-wordpress-plugins/&#34;&gt;wordpress plugin I use&lt;/a&gt;. Well since then a lot of my favorite plugins have been consolidated or are now obsolete with the improvements to the wordpress platform. From that list of 10 I put out two years ago I’m still running 7 of them &lt;a href=&#34;http://wordpress.org/plugins/kpicasa-gallery/&#34;&gt;kPicasa Gallery&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;http://wordpress.org/extend/plugins/google-analytics-for-wordpress/&#34;&gt;Google Analytics for WordPress&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;http://wordpress.org/extend/plugins/xbox-gamertag-widget/&#34;&gt;XBOX Live Gamertag&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;http://wordpress.org/extend/plugins/akismet/&#34;&gt;Akismet&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;http://urbangiraffe.com/plugins/redirection/&#34;&gt;Redirection&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.wesg.ca/2008/08/wordpress-widget-most-popular/&#34;&gt;Most Popular Posts&lt;/a&gt;. But the latest ones I can’t live without are &lt;a href=&#34;http://wordpress.org/plugins/jetpack/&#34;&gt;Jetpack&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;http://wordpress.org/plugins/kb-advanced-rss-widget/&#34;&gt;KB Advanced RSS Widget&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&#34;http://wordpress.org/plugins/backupwordpress/&#34;&gt;BackUpWordPress&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best Practices For Automating Business Processes with Kapow</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/rpa/best-practices-for-automating-business-processes-with-kapow/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/rpa/best-practices-for-automating-business-processes-with-kapow/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Thanks for attending my session on best practices for automation business processes with Kapow at the &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.kapow-wow.com/&#34;&gt;2013 Kapow.Wow User Summit&lt;/a&gt;. As promised in the session i wanted to share my slides for all.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;iframe src=&#34;https://onedrive.live.com/embed?cid=85BF2A35D22B167F&amp;resid=85BF2A35D22B167F%216705&amp;authkey=AAnLAX5A3W8n3Xs&amp;em=2&#34; width=&#34;402&#34; height=&#34;327&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; scrolling=&#34;no&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Limit Yourself</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2013-02-06-why-limit-yourself/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2013 11:41:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2013-02-06-why-limit-yourself/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:black;font-family:Helvetica;font-size:10pt;background-color:white;&#34;&gt;We join the Jaycees so that we can grow as individuals, expand ourselves personally, and to help humanity. Part of growing ourselves is taking advantage of all the opportunities that we’re presented with in life. Your membership to our great organization allows you many opportunities to do things that you can only dreamed of. You can drive positive change in your community and around the world. You can help build a park for neighborhood kids, you help fight diseases around the world, and you can meet world leaders and discuss your thoughts on global issues. Since joining the Jaycees in 2004 I’ve had the opportunity to meet people all around the world who are members of this great organization, I’ve had the opportunity see people make these positive changes in their community. I’ve had the opportunity to save hundreds of lives. You can develop your leadership skills further beyond what any collegiate course could offer. I think about how I’ve been given this opportunity to help lead and plot the course of one the largest Jaycee organizations in the world in 2013. The Jaycees give you the tools, the training, and the knowledge to dream and achieve. But you must not limit yourself you can accomplish anything you want. Let me ask you two questions, what do you want to accomplish? &amp;amp; how can we do it together?&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Four Component Approach</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/jci/the-four-component-approach/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/jci/the-four-component-approach/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Jaycees as you all know by now is more than just a community service organization. Since the founding in 1915 it has held true to its primary purpose of building young leaders to tackle the challenges of tomorrow. In 2013 I will be servicing you as your State Membership Development vice President; the Member Development area encompasses four key components and all them vital. First Recruit since our organization is based on membership requirements it’s important that we replace those that no longer meet our requirements to be members. One of the best ways to end the year positive is to plan on replacing the members who will not meet your chapter’s requirements for membership right away. The second component is Orientation, once a new member joins our organization it is essential that we teach them about what they just joined and how they can make their mark on your chapter and their community. Did you know your Region and state staff can provide assistance with planning and or conducting your training? The third component and my personal favorite is Activation. It&amp;rsquo;s no secret why people stay in our organization and it certainly no secret why they leave. But we can prevent a large portion of them from doing by getting them involved. On numerous times I&amp;rsquo;ve seen members for the first time get involved with our organizations at social&amp;rsquo;s, or local food drives. The fourth component is Retention; did you know the hardest thing do for most of our chapter isn&amp;rsquo;t just to retain a member it’s to show them the value of continuing their membership in our organization? Each person joined the organization for a different reason then the last. Understanding what they are looking to get out of our organization will help you understand how to retain them. A survey of your membership each year is great start. They don’t have to be lengthy just ask the most important questions. The most important part is the actions they see come out of the survey. Another way is get down and dirty with your members. When I was a local director I was assigned to a group members our chapter considered be at risk for lost during the year. These were members who we were pretty sure we would need to replace throughout the year. I regularly called every one of these members, course I left a lot of messages but I would call anyway, I would send them emails updating them on what happened at the last meeting including anything funny, I would send them birthday card during their birthday’s months and so forth. The whole point is to make them feel as if they were getting a value out of their membership. At the end of the year we were able to retain about 85% of those members. But without any effort or dedication we would have lost 100% of them. In 2013 keep on growing as young leaders, leaving your mark on your communities, and sharing the Jaycees every opportunity you can. But make sure your teaching your members too and getting them all involved in their chapters and together we can all Make Our Mark !!!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 Apps I Loved In 2012</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2012-12-31-10-apps-i-loved-in-2012/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2012 09:20:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2012-12-31-10-apps-i-loved-in-2012/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Now that we’re in the final day of 2012 I figure it was a great time to toast the apps that make my life easier throughout the year. These apps are crossed platform you can use them and their services on both Android, IPhone, and in some cases Blackberry.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.tripit&#34;&gt;Tripit&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.evernote&#34;&gt;Evernote&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.spotify.mobile.android.ui&#34;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.hulu.plus&#34;&gt;Hulu&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.netflix.mediaclient&#34;&gt;Netflix&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=flipboard.app&#34;&gt;Flipboard&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=gbis.gbandroid&#34;&gt;Gasbuddy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.amazon.kindle&#34;&gt;Amazon Kindle Reader&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.microsoft.smartglass&#34;&gt;Xbox 360 Smartglass&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.jerrellmardis.ridemetra&#34;&gt;Ride Metra&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started With Microsoft Access</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/sql/getting-started-with-microsoft-access/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/sql/getting-started-with-microsoft-access/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve been using Microsoft Access since Access 97 it&amp;rsquo;s a very powerful tool is you use it right. You can use it for everything from personal Baseball card inventory control to managing home inventories; even fortune 500 companies use it to manage million dollar systems. As I said if you use it right it can be quite a powerful tool built on some amazing framework. Recently a friend who&amp;rsquo;s getting into access asked me if I could provide him some resources so that he can get better familiar with the tool. Below is a list of resources I put together for him.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intro To Kapow Katalyst</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/rpa/intro-to-kapow-katalyst/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/rpa/intro-to-kapow-katalyst/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This will be the first posting of a new category on my blog regard Kapow Software a Robotic Process Automation (RPA) tool. Before I begin to discuss my usage experiences and technical information regarding Kapow Katalyst, I figure it would be good to give a little background about it. Kapow Katalyst is a Web Data Aggregation Tool; these tools are used to capture data from websites for analytic&amp;rsquo;s purposes. Where Kapow excels is it allows you to complete your ETL process from a single execution aka a Robot. Robots can get pretty detailed in length and if you&amp;rsquo;re reusing code across multiple robots you can insert snippets instead of rewriting the code. Check out the video below for more information regarding this product.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Passion</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2012-11-20-my-passion/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2012 14:37:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2012-11-20-my-passion/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;When I interviewed with &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.coyote.com&#34;&gt;Coyote&lt;/a&gt; a discussion came up of passion and I said my passion at work was turning data into insight for my coworkers. During my presentation about myself to our Executive team and my coworkers I realized what my true passion is… it’s to help people. Every job I’ve had involved helping people and at &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.coyote.com&#34;&gt;Coyote&lt;/a&gt; it’s no different I’m just using my technical skills to help our coworkers and our customers; outside work I love to volunteer with the &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.usjaycees.org&#34;&gt;Jaycees&lt;/a&gt; because we help people and make an impact with the work we do around the world. In our organization’s creed we’ve got this line that can sum it all up for me &lt;em&gt;“Service to Humanity Is the Best Work of Life”&lt;/em&gt; so let me ask you what is your passion?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHS Just Chugging Along</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2012-11-20-whs-just-chugging-along/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2012 13:51:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2012-11-20-whs-just-chugging-along/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.gogorichie.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/11/112012_1951_WHSJustChug1.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt; It’s true when they say no news is good news, my Windows Home Server has been just chugging along currently were approaching 180 days without rebooting, which is quite impressive to even to me. Actually now that think about it I made a major change to my setup &lt;img src=&#34;https://www.gogorichie.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/11/112012_1951_WHSJustChug2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;back in March. I purchased a Dell PowerEdge 700 for 25 dollars on eBay which a real server instead of an old desktop I had lying around. This was a major performance increase and adds additional room to the cabinet for more hard drives, I think like another 2 or 4 which I’m thinking of throwing all my old drives into the pool to just max out the space. Also I’m not sure what to do with the tape drive currently installed.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Querying The Most Recent Records</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/sql/querying-the-most-recent-records/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/sql/querying-the-most-recent-records/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Here’s another fun solution for you business intelligence people out there. Suppose you wanted to pull data that was updated in the last 15mins based on when a row was last. I&amp;rsquo;m sure there are many ways to accomplish this but I like to use the &lt;a href=&#34;http://msdn.microsoft.com/en-us/library/ms186819.aspx&#34;&gt;DATEADD() function&lt;/a&gt; in Microsoft SQL Server 2008. Below is the query using the &lt;a href=&#34;http://msftdbprodsamples.codeplex.com/&#34;&gt;AdventureWorks2008R2&lt;/a&gt; database enjoy.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-family: Lucida Console; font-size: 10pt;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: blue;&#34;&gt;SELECT&lt;/span&gt; I&lt;span style=&#34;color: gray;&#34;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;ProductID&lt;span style=&#34;color: gray;&#34;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; I&lt;span style=&#34;color: gray;&#34;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;LocationID&lt;span style=&#34;color: gray;&#34;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; I&lt;span style=&#34;color: gray;&#34;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;Bin&lt;span style=&#34;color: gray;&#34;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; I&lt;span style=&#34;color: gray;&#34;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;Shelf&lt;span style=&#34;color: gray;&#34;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; I&lt;span style=&#34;color: gray;&#34;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;Quantity&lt;span style=&#34;color: gray;&#34;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; P&lt;span style=&#34;color: gray;&#34;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;ProductNumber&lt;span style=&#34;color: gray;&#34;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; P&lt;span style=&#34;color: gray;&#34;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;Name&lt;span style=&#34;color: gray;&#34;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; I&lt;span style=&#34;color: gray;&#34;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;ModifiedDate&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Serving As 2013 State Vice President</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2012-09-12-2013statevp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2012 10:06:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2012-09-12-2013statevp/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.gogorichie.com/wp-content/uploads/2011/08/081211_1218_2.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.gogorichie.com/wp-content/uploads/2011/08/081211_1218_2.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; title=&#34;081211_1218_2.png&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;On September 8&lt;sup&gt;th&lt;/sup&gt; my campaign to serve the Illinois Jaycees members as their 2013 Membership Development Vice President came to end with me being elected. It’s true competing for the time of our members has gotten tougher each year our chapter, region, and state boards have gotten stretched too thin, burned out quickly, not adequately trained and weaker. As a result our members have suffered. Next year I want to focus on shaping the future of our organization. First increase involvement in the passports to leaders program to develop our future leaders at the chapter level, Offer new membership development opportunities across the state to grow our chapters, Strengthen our weaker chapters through education of tools, resources, new tactics on how to resolve their local problems. Develop and lead an extension task force to assist chapters and regions in their completion more than half the extension completed each failed by the end of the second year, what if we could reduce that by 2 or 3 chapters. Bring new networking opportunities to our members to further add value to their membership. In 2013 I’m bringing the right &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;r&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;esources needed to recruit, retain, and develop our fellow Jaycees !!!!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A New Journey</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2012-09-05-new-journey/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2012 09:37:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2012-09-05-new-journey/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;August 20th was my last day at Sears Holdings. I once heard somewhere the average person my age spends three years at a job before leaving and move on. Well I sent 12 years there of course I held four different roles there during that time. I decided to leave Sears Holdings because the opportunity presented to me to join Coyote Logistics and learn &amp;amp; develop new systems was too great to pass up. Of course I’m still writing SSIS packages, Using SQL day in and day out but I’m automating things and developing new processes on a whole new level using the greatest and latest tools on the market. Who is Coyote Logistics and what they do? Well Coyote Logistic is a 3&lt;sup&gt;rd&lt;/sup&gt; party logistics service provider based out of Chicago they specialize in moving customer shipments in the most efficient manner for their customers, their drivers, and the environment. So with lots of cargo moving around the world all the time, there is a lot of data for me to work with, simplify, and share with my coworkers and our customers.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wheeling Jaycees Social Media 101</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2012-07-29-social-media-101/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jul 2012 19:33:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2012-07-29-social-media-101/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.gogorichie.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/07/073012_0033_SocialMedia1.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:#666666;font-family:Verdana;font-size:9pt;&#34;&gt;Every wonder why some people have amazing looking Facebook profiles or 1000s of followers? In this 30 minute session we will discuss how to use facebook, google+, twitter the simple and easy way to communicate with your friends, family, and followers. This course is led me Richard Lewis a veteran user of social media sites and Chairman of the US Jaycees National Technology Advisory Committee. Come out next month on August 7&lt;sup&gt;th&lt;/sup&gt; at 7:00PM. You can &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.meetup.com/WheelingJaycees/events/75088202/&#34;&gt;RSVP&lt;/a&gt; on the Wheeling Jaycees Meetup site .&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SQL Saturday 119 Recap In 189 Words</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/sql/sql-saturday-119-recap-in-189-words/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/sql/sql-saturday-119-recap-in-189-words/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://gogorichiesitefiles.blob.core.windows.net/publicfiles/sql_saturday_logo.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So I&amp;rsquo;m about a month late or maybe three in writing my recap on the event so here goes. It was awesomeness !!!! 2012 marked my second SQL Saturday that I&amp;rsquo;ve attended and have to say it just keeps getting better. This year I was able to volunteer with registration which is an awesome way to meet all the attendees well at least most of them. Also I hooped into five awesome sessions &amp;ldquo;A Complete BI Solution in About an Hour!&amp;rdquo; With &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.aaronstanleyking.com/&#34;&gt;Arron King&lt;/a&gt;, SRS Report Builder for Business Intelligence with David Eichner, Kama Sutra of SSIS: A guide to loving ETL with &lt;a href=&#34;http://billfellows.blogspot.com/&#34;&gt;Bill Fellows&lt;/a&gt;, and The Script Task, powerhouse of SSIS with &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.gerasus.com/&#34;&gt;Norman Kelm&lt;/a&gt;, and Join Us! Getting Started as a Technical Speaker with &lt;a href=&#34;http://indydba.com/&#34;&gt;Eddie Wuerch&lt;/a&gt; cause I would love to start speaking at SQL events outside of work. Biggest take a way&amp;rsquo;s from this year event was networking with others in the profession and the knowledge I picked up from all the sessions. I&amp;rsquo;m already looking forward to the 2013 event.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>April Meme 15 Assignment</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/sql/april-meme15-assignment/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/sql/april-meme15-assignment/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- ![](http://mattvelic.com/wp-content/uploads/2011/12/meme15new.png)  --&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Another #Meme 15 topic brought you by MVP Jason Strate (&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.jasonstrate.com/&#34;&gt;Blog&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&#34;http://twitter.com/#!/stratesql&#34;&gt;twitter&lt;/a&gt;). This month topic &lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;What are ten blogs that you think other SQL Server professionals should be following but might not be?&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt; Coming up with a list of just 10 is harder than I thought narrowing it down to ten is just way to hard but i was able to do. The list I  put together covers everyone from the newbie to SQL to the all-round DBA.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Living the Windows 8 Experience</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2012-03-24-living-the-windows-8-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2012 21:43:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2012-03-24-living-the-windows-8-experience/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.gogorichie.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/03/032512_0243_LivingtheWi1.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Introduction&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I downloaded Windows 8 when it was released to Developers back last year and installed it on a virtual workstation with a 2 gigs of ram running from my Windows Home Server. I thought it was shaky and slow. So I decided to abandon it. Until recently when the Consumer Preview release came out and I decided to give it another try. Getting windows 8 up running was actually quite simple. Downloaded the Consumer release preview and burned the ISO to a DVD was all that was required. Besides an operating system key of course. I decided to install windows 8 my primary laptop Toshiba T205 Satellite laptop so that I can get a full experience by using it day in and day out. Just a few specs on my laptop has 160gb hard drive 2gb of ram and is running a Intel Dual Core Pentium 1.6ghz processor so nothing fancy and no touch screen. But this being a five year old computer I expected for the operating system to sluggish.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quick &amp; Simple Inner Join</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/sql/quick-simple-inner-join/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/sql/quick-simple-inner-join/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A business partner approached me the other day looking to share information with my company. Since parts numbers are recycled more often than lame jokes in my business one of the things we needed the business partner to provide was the brand of the part. The business partner said that this would be difficult to do since they were unfamiliar with linking data across tables in any manner. After understanding a little about the setup of the partner&amp;rsquo;s tables I taught them to design a view linking the two primary tables where the data could be seen together through a view. Since their tables where normalized all they needed was an &lt;a href=&#34;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Inner_join&#34;&gt;INNER JOIN&lt;/a&gt; statement to make this happen. Below is a sample of the statement i wrote for the partner.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meme 15 Why Did I Start Blogging</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/sql/why-did-i-start-blogging/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/sql/why-did-i-start-blogging/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This month&amp;rsquo;s &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.jasonstrate.com/2011/12/the-meme15-on-social-networking/&#34;&gt;Meme15&lt;/a&gt; assignment and the first was chosen by Jason Strate (&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.jasonstrate.com/&#34;&gt;Blog&lt;/a&gt;|&lt;a href=&#34;http://twitter.com/&#34;&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;) he posed the assignment of writing about why do I blog and why I started.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I started blogging back in &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.gogorichie.com/%E2%80%8E&#34;&gt;2003&lt;/a&gt; just about a one year after launching Gogorichie.com, back then it was the social network of its time along with AIM and YIM. As me and my high school friends went off to college we stayed in contact via our blogs. You know this topic made me go back to the very beginning and read my very first blog posting. It brought up memories of living in LA and the good times I had out there. Wait most of those post were written after coming home from a night out so a lot of the postings were run but all fun.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>T-SQL Tuesday 025 - My Favorite Little Trick</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/sql/my-favorite-little-trick/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/sql/my-favorite-little-trick/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://gogorichiesitefiles.blob.core.windows.net/publicfiles/tsqltuesday.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;T-SQL Tusday&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This month&amp;rsquo;s T-SQL Tuesday topic is from &lt;a href=&#34;http://sqlblog.com/blogs/allen_white/default.aspx&#34;&gt;Allen White&lt;/a&gt;. He posed the question of what is my favorite little SQL trick. I can&amp;rsquo;t wait to see what tips the &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/#!/search?q=%23sqlfamily&#34;&gt;#SQLFamily&lt;/a&gt; write about. I discovered one of my favorite tricks last year, just a little background my first SQL version I started out administrating and developing on 8 years ago was SQL 2000 back then to get table statistics was no easy task. These days you just need to right-click on the database and go the reports to get much of the information you&amp;rsquo;ll need about a database. I started using SQL 2008 last year so when I when wrote a &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.gogorichie.com/2010/05/determing-sql-server-table-size-tip/&#34;&gt;blog post&lt;/a&gt; about this little trick I came across online on how to quickly pull the table size information it had been one of my favorite tricks then. Since I&amp;rsquo;m still dealing with data in SQL 2000 server production environment still this trick still comes in handy. Thanks to the posting by &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.mitchelsellers.com/&#34;&gt;Mitchel Sellers&lt;/a&gt; on &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.mitchelsellers.com/blogs/articletype/articleview/articleid/121/determing-sql-server-table-size.aspx&#34;&gt;How to Determine Table Size&lt;/a&gt; it&amp;rsquo;s become quick and easy to get the information I need about my databases.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meme Monday: What SQLFamily Means To Me</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/sql/sqlfamily-means-to-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/sql/sqlfamily-means-to-me/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I saw this topic a few weeks back on &lt;a href=&#34;http://thomaslarock.com/2011/11/meme-monday-for-november/&#34;&gt;@sqlrockstar&lt;/a&gt;&amp;rsquo;s site but never got around to writing a post.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve been in working on databases for about 6 years now a mixture of Access, SQL, Teradata, and MySQL. So when I saw the topic thoughts began to flow through my brain. What does the SQL Family mean to me?? it means that there is a network of people with the same interest, challenged by the same problems as me. Now with my discovery of twitter, hence the hashtag I’ve been able to discovered the family and discovered local events such as the user groups in Chicago and SQL Saturday&amp;rsquo;s events and many others including a yearly &lt;a href=&#34;http://sqlcruise.com/&#34;&gt;cruise&lt;/a&gt;. Now when i need help with programming question I can turn to the &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/#!/search?q=%23sqlfamily&#34;&gt;#sqlfamily&lt;/a&gt;, the people are so cool that when its someone&amp;rsquo;s birthday or other special occasion they get acknowledged by the &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/#!/search?q=%23sqlfamily&#34;&gt;#sqlfamily&lt;/a&gt; or even a sad event the family member off words of comfort.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nothing But Nets News Flash !!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2011-11-02-nothing-but-nets-news-flash/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2011 18:34:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2011-11-02-nothing-but-nets-news-flash/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Great News Everyone, I talked to Anthony Colletti today via email. He’s in Brussels Belgium at the JCI World Congress and said that were *#3 in the&lt;br&gt;&#xA;WORLD* for JCI organizations in raising money for Nothing But Nets !!!!! just think how much more we can achieve by the end of the year. For every $10 we raise we save a life from Malaria donate at &lt;a href=&#34;http://bit.ly/ut25Oh&#34;&gt;http://bit.ly/ut25Oh&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Richard Lewis&lt;br&gt;&#xA;2011 Website Program Manager – United States Jaycees&lt;br&gt;&#xA;2011 National Prog/ Govt. Involvement State Chair – Illinois Jaycees&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nothing But Nets Fundraising Update</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2011-09-14-nothing-but-nets-fundraising-update-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2011 10:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2011-09-14-nothing-but-nets-fundraising-update-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https:///iljaycees.org/wp-content/uploads/2011/09/nets.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;What an awesome GA we had this past weekend!!! Saturday during Lunch Anthony Colletti spoke about how close we are the our 2011 Nothing But Nets goal and our chapters STEPPED UP big time…to the tune of $1051.00 in pledges and donations. A big thanks goes out to all those chapters Mount Prospect, Gurnee/Lindenhurst, Bolingbrook, Chatham, Woodstock, Lombard, and Woodridge. Once we receive all the checks we will be only $289 away from our goal !!! please consider making a donation of 10 bucks to our &lt;a href=&#34;http://bit.ly/thedrivefor289&#34;&gt;State Nothing But Nets Site&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bringing the T.K.O</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2011-09-05-bringing-the-t-k-o/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2011 09:43:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2011-09-05-bringing-the-t-k-o/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Last friday was exciting I announced my candidacy for 2012 Area One Vice President of the Illinois Jaycees. I believe that we can grow our area with outstanding Training held locally, We can use the Knowledge of our members and our networks to strengthen our area, and We can retain our members through all the Opportunities our organization have to offer. Like my page on Facebook at &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.facebook.com/Voteforrichard&#34;&gt;http://www.facebook.com/Voteforrichard&lt;/a&gt; and follow my campaign. Since our organizations election is less then two weeks away I’m visiting 14 chapters in 13 days with a three day vacation in the middle of my campaign. I want to get out and hear from our members what are their concerns across the Area chapters in the Fox Valley may have different concerns then chapters in the Northeast or Northwest.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaycees and Politics</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/jci/jaycees-and-politics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/jci/jaycees-and-politics/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As Jaycee members we have a long history of driving change in our communities across the country and all through our grassroots skills and efforts. For example, when a group of young business men in the Los Angeles area were dissatisfied with their representation in congress they sought out a candidate and came across a young who was a Jaycee their first reaction was here is a young man who has been through the best training in the world. This particular Jaycee won their confidence and was elected to serve them in congress. He went on to serve his country as our nation&amp;rsquo;s President. Here&amp;rsquo;s another example of Jaycees and politics; Did you know Bill Clinton, Al Gore, Gerald Ford, Ralph Nader, Dick Chaney, Joe Biden and many more were all TOYA recipients? Still need more proof you say&amp;hellip;. ever hear of the Young Republicans Party? Well it was founded by then Jaycees National President George H. Olmsted in 1932 after being called upon by US President Herbert Hoover who was looking for a way to get more young men out to vote and involved in politics. Speaking of getting out to vote did you know that &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.usjaycees.org/index.php/government-involvement&#34;&gt;Get Out The Vote&lt;/a&gt; is our very own national program for the Jaycees organization under the Government Involvement area? Which mean each chapter should and is encouraged to run a project to support this program. The easiest thing to do is to run a voter registration drive in your community at one of your town festivals or events. A toolkit can be downloaded from &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.usjaycees.org/index.php/government-involvement&#34;&gt;http://www.usjaycees.org/index.php/government-involvement&lt;/a&gt; and information on how you can best serve your local community can be found through your local County Clerks office.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Founding Of The Abbeville Jaycees</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/jci/abbeville-jaycees/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/jci/abbeville-jaycees/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- ![Robert E. Condon](http://usjayceefoundation.org/history/1920/images/RobertECondon_med.jpg &#34;Robert E. Condon&#34;) --&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Over the weekend I read another chapter of the book Young Men Can Change The World. I came across another great story this one of how the Abbeville Jaycees was founded. The story was a recount of the adventure of at the time U.S. Jaycees National Vice President &lt;a href=&#34;http://usjayceefoundation.org/history/1920/1926/index.htm&#34;&gt;Robert E. Condon&lt;/a&gt; who at the age of 29 also held the position of civil defense commissioner for the greater New York metro area. Condon decided to use his position in both the Jaycees and personally to grow the organization as well as help his community by introducing an airmail service from New York to Atlanta. After introducing his plan the two cities and U.S. Post Office were excited to put it into action. During their first flight from Atlanta the plane developed troubles over South Carolina with Condon at co-pilot which ended with a crashing landing in a  farm field outside the town of Abbeville, SC. After hitching hiking into town Condon was interviewed by the local newspaper reporter he began to tell him that this was the inaugural flight of The United States Junior Chamber airmail program when the reporter said The United States what????? Well just like Jaycees do theses days when presented with the opportunity of spreading our message. Condon told the reporter all about the Jaycees by night fall he rounded up a group of young men typed out a charter for the &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.greenwoodjaycees.org/&#34;&gt;Abbeville Junior Chamber Of Commerce&lt;/a&gt; and had their charter fee in his pocket. The plane never made it to New York but as result of Robert&amp;rsquo;s trip it resulted in the founding of the &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.greenwoodjaycees.org/&#34;&gt;Abbeville Jaycees&lt;/a&gt; chapter. Condon went on to meet Charles Lindbergh while waiting for a flight and invite him to our organization and serve as our 7th Junior Chamber National President.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outstanding Young Farmers</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2011-05-13-outstanding-young-farmers/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2011 10:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2011-05-13-outstanding-young-farmers/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://iljaycees.org/wp-content/uploads/2011/05/image.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://iljaycees.org/wp-content/uploads/2011/05/image_thumb.png&#34; alt=&#34;OYF banner&#34; title=&#34;OYF banner&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Since 1954 Outstanding Young Farmers has been a signature program of the US Jaycees and believe it or not we’ve got very little to do with. now i know that’s hard to believe that the largest Jaycee state and is covered by 80% of farm land hasn’t Produce an Outstanding Young Farmer since 2008. Well that changes this year, because our states goal is to submit 5 outstanding candidates for this award. The requirements for submission of this award is simple they must be in Jaycee age range, they must be actual farm operators, deriving a minimum of two-thirds of their income from farming, and All information on the nomination form must be completed. The cost of nominating someone to your chapter is free because it is sponsored by John Deere and as a bonus for submitting you can earn POC points for your chapter. So there’s no reason why our chapters in farming communities can’t submit at least one nominee.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What’s Our Impact So Far</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2011-05-11-whats-our-impact-so-far/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2011 12:48:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2011-05-11-whats-our-impact-so-far/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.globalproblems-globalsolutions.org/site/TR/Events/NBN?pg=team&amp;amp;fr_id=1040&amp;amp;team_id=4161&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.gogorichie.com/wp-content/uploads/2011/05/image.png&#34; alt=&#34;image&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt; As i write this i reflect back on January when State VP Geno asked me what was my Goal for Nothing But Nets? I pondered for a second and said I want to double what we made in 2010 and I wrote down $3000 dollars and then i started to wonder could we really do it? Well I’m excited to say that in just 5 months we’ve crossed the $3,000 dollar mark and were still going. That’s huge in my book Illinois Jaycees put their brains together and thought of ways they could help some chapters ran Bar Olympics for the cause while other chapters ran change collection drives. If you haven’t done so visit our donation website and make a contribution to help save a life &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.globalproblems-globalsolutions.org/site/TR/Events/NBN?pg=team&amp;amp;fr_id=1040&amp;amp;team_id=4161&#34;&gt;http://www.globalproblems-globalsolutions.org/site/TR/Events/NBN?pg=team&amp;amp;fr_id=1040&amp;amp;team_id=4161&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scholarship Opportunities</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2011-04-08-scholarship-opportunities/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2011 10:16:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2011-04-08-scholarship-opportunities/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:black;font-family:Trebuchet MS;&#34;&gt;By Richard Lewis&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:black;font-family:Trebuchet MS;&#34;&gt;National Programs &amp;amp; Government Involvement State Chairmen&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:blue;font-family:Trebuchet MS;text-decoration:underline;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;mailto:Richard.lewis@iljaycees.org&#34;&gt;Richard.lewis@iljaycees.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:black;font-family:Arial;&#34;&gt;It’s that wonderful time of year if you’re a student the nice weather outside may signal the near end of another year and it’s the time when most Jaycee chapters give away there annual scholarship to students in their communities. But did you know that as a Jaycee member you and your family are eligible for FIVE scholarship programs funded by our organization? There are three from The U.S. Jaycee Foundation and two from our very own Illinois Jaycees Charitable Foundation below is a little information about each scholarship program and the requirements. If you have any additional questions feel free to email me at &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:Richard.Lewis@iljaycees.org&#34;&gt;Richard.Lewis@iljaycees.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Support Our Troops Update</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2011-04-04-support-our-troops-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2011 10:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2011-04-04-support-our-troops-update/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.supportourtroops.org/index.php?option=com_k2&amp;amp;view=item&amp;amp;id=1735:danville-jaycees-step-up-for-the-troops&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https:///iljaycees.org/wp-content/uploads/2011/04/thumb_il-jayceesspaghettidinnersignage.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; title=&#34;Danville  Jaycees “Coalition for the Willing”&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Want to win 100 bucks? This year’s National Chair for the Support Our Troops program has setup a facebook group to communicate challenges and project ideas to directly to chapter members.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;She is running a challenge, she wants the chapters around country to send their completed CPG’s to her for projects they’ve ran this year by June 1st and she will give the best one selected One Hundred Bucks. Join her group at &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.facebook.com/pages/US-Jaycees-Support-Our-TroopsToys-for-Tots-Program/112406932168921&#34;&gt;http://www.facebook.com/pages/US-Jaycees-Support-Our-TroopsToys-for-Tots-Program/112406932168921&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meme Monday 4-4-11</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/sql/meme-monday-4-4-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/sql/meme-monday-4-4-11/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;First off shout out to &lt;a href=&#34;http://thomaslarock.com/2011/04/welcome-to-meme-monday/&#34;&gt;Thomas Larock&lt;/a&gt; for coming up with this idea. Today’s meme is “Write a SQL blog post in 11 words or less”, and here is my entry: &lt;em&gt;Write query. Syntax error. Search Google. run query again. Happy dance!!!!&lt;/em&gt; Some more shout outs to my favorite readings from last month: * Pinal Dave (&lt;a href=&#34;http://blog.sqlauthority.com/&#34;&gt;Blog&lt;/a&gt; | @&lt;a href=&#34;http://twitter.com/pinaldave&#34;&gt;pinaldave&lt;/a&gt;) * Brent Ozar (&lt;a href=&#34;http://brentozar.com/&#34;&gt;Blog&lt;/a&gt; | @&lt;a href=&#34;http://twitter.com/BrentO&#34;&gt;BrentO&lt;/a&gt;) * Thomas Larock (&lt;a href=&#34;http://thomaslarock.com/&#34;&gt;Blog&lt;/a&gt; | @&lt;a href=&#34;http://twitter.com/SQLRockstar&#34;&gt;sqlrockstar&lt;/a&gt;) * BIDN (&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.bidn.com/blogs/&#34;&gt;Blog&lt;/a&gt; | @&lt;a href=&#34;http://twitter.com/bidn&#34;&gt;bidn&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remember To Vote</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2011-03-10-remember-to-vote/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2011 14:51:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2011-03-10-remember-to-vote/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.gogorichie.com/wp-content/uploads/2011/03/031011_2051_RememberToV12.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;I was reading a section of a Book called Young Men Can Change The World the other day and wanted to share it with you. It told the story of group Jaycee members out in California who were so passionate with some the legislation being passed in their community that they put together a committee to find someone from their community to run for Representative. After months of searching they found a young Jaycee member who was a lawyer and encouraged him to run, with their support and determination not to lose he went on to win and get elected. At the age of 34 he was recognized by the US Junior Chamber as a Ten Outstanding American. Then just three years later in 1950 he was elected Senator from California and in 1953 he went on to become our nations 36&lt;sup&gt;th&lt;/sup&gt; Vice President and a few year later our nation’s 37&lt;sup&gt;th&lt;/sup&gt; President. This man was Richard M. Nixon and for his efforts and involvement with the Jaycees movement over the years was he was recognized as JCI Senator # 72. Remember to vote on Tuesday April 5&lt;sup&gt;th&lt;/sup&gt;. A list of local voting polls can be founded at &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.vote411.org/pollfinder.php&#34;&gt;http://www.vote411.org/pollfinder.php&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remember To Vote</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/jci/remember-to-vote/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/jci/remember-to-vote/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- ![](https:///www.gogorichie.com/wp-content/uploads/2011/03/031011_2051_RememberToV12.jpg) --&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I was reading a section of a Book called Young Men Can Change The World the other day and wanted to share it with you. It told the story of group Jaycee members out in California who were so passionate with some the legislation being passed in their community that they put together a committee to find someone from their community to run for Representative. After months of searching they found a young Jaycee member who was a lawyer and encouraged him to run, with their support and determination not to lose he went on to win and get elected. At the age of 34 he was recognized by the US Junior Chamber as a Ten Outstanding American. Then just three years later in 1950 he was elected Senator from California and in 1953 he went on to become our nations 36th Vice President and a few year later our nation&amp;rsquo;s 37th President. This man was Richard M. Nixon and for his efforts and involvement with the Jaycees movement over the years was he was recognized as JCI Senator # 72. Remember to vote on Tuesday April 5th. A list of local voting polls can be founded at &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.vote411.org/pollfinder.php&#34;&gt;http://www.vote411.org/pollfinder.php&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Our Impact Then and Now</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2011-02-11-our-impact-then-and-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2011 15:16:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2011-02-11-our-impact-then-and-now/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:black;font-family:Times New Roman;&#34;&gt;Richard Lewis&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:black;font-family:Times New Roman;&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;National Programs and Government Involvement State Chairmen&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.gogorichie.com/wp-content/uploads/2011/12/121911_2115_OurImpactTh1.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:black;font-family:Times New Roman;&#34;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-family:Times New Roman;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:black;&#34;&gt;In 1954 Jaycees from many nations provided medical relief to the hundreds of thousands of Vietnamese refugees fleeing North Viet Nam. This became one of our first big international projects; it was known as operation brotherhood and brought international attention to the US Jaycees and our international organization JCI around the globe. When I think of the line in our creed &lt;em&gt;“The Brotherhood of man transcends the Sovereignty of Nations”&lt;/em&gt; It makes me think back about the Jaycee organization over the years and our acceptances of each other and our commitment to help heal the world and make it a better place. In 2008 we found that as members we can fight and save lives and stopped malaria and so we took to it and got involved with the United Nations program Nothing But Nets. In 2010, Jaycee members raised more than USD $500,000, which doubles campaign donations from the previous two years. This impact has led to the purchase and distribution of more than 50,000 life-saving bed nets in Africa. Our goal this year in the state is $3,000 that translates to 300 lives we can impact. As members you can help by Send a message to all your friends through Facebook, LinkedIn, Twitter or whatever social media network you use to get the word out about the dangers of malaria. Let them know how they can contribute a net through our state nothing but nets fundraising site or your chapter nothing but nets site, and encourage them to get the word out to all their friends. More information about the Illinois Jaycees involvement with this national program can be found at &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.google.com/url?q=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.globalproblems-globalsolutions.org%2Fgoto%2F2011iljaycees&amp;amp;sa=D&amp;amp;sntz=1&amp;amp;usg=AFQjCNHf7VL-KhmodulCK_eIa7OQSTI6Jw&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:blue;text-decoration:underline;&#34;&gt;http&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.google.com/url?q=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.globalproblems-globalsolutions.org%2Fgoto%2F2011iljaycees&amp;amp;sa=D&amp;amp;sntz=1&amp;amp;usg=AFQjCNHf7VL-KhmodulCK_eIa7OQSTI6Jw&#34;&gt;://&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.google.com/url?q=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.globalproblems-globalsolutions.org%2Fgoto%2F2011iljaycees&amp;amp;sa=D&amp;amp;sntz=1&amp;amp;usg=AFQjCNHf7VL-KhmodulCK_eIa7OQSTI6Jw&#34;&gt;www&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.google.com/url?q=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.globalproblems-globalsolutions.org%2Fgoto%2F2011iljaycees&amp;amp;sa=D&amp;amp;sntz=1&amp;amp;usg=AFQjCNHf7VL-KhmodulCK_eIa7OQSTI6Jw&#34;&gt;.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.google.com/url?q=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.globalproblems-globalsolutions.org%2Fgoto%2F2011iljaycees&amp;amp;sa=D&amp;amp;sntz=1&amp;amp;usg=AFQjCNHf7VL-KhmodulCK_eIa7OQSTI6Jw&#34;&gt;globalproblems&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.google.com/url?q=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.globalproblems-globalsolutions.org%2Fgoto%2F2011iljaycees&amp;amp;sa=D&amp;amp;sntz=1&amp;amp;usg=AFQjCNHf7VL-KhmodulCK_eIa7OQSTI6Jw&#34;&gt;–&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.google.com/url?q=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.globalproblems-globalsolutions.org%2Fgoto%2F2011iljaycees&amp;amp;sa=D&amp;amp;sntz=1&amp;amp;usg=AFQjCNHf7VL-KhmodulCK_eIa7OQSTI6Jw&#34;&gt;globalsolutions&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.google.com/url?q=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.globalproblems-globalsolutions.org%2Fgoto%2F2011iljaycees&amp;amp;sa=D&amp;amp;sntz=1&amp;amp;usg=AFQjCNHf7VL-KhmodulCK_eIa7OQSTI6Jw&#34;&gt;.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.google.com/url?q=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.globalproblems-globalsolutions.org%2Fgoto%2F2011iljaycees&amp;amp;sa=D&amp;amp;sntz=1&amp;amp;usg=AFQjCNHf7VL-KhmodulCK_eIa7OQSTI6Jw&#34;&gt;org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.google.com/url?q=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.globalproblems-globalsolutions.org%2Fgoto%2F2011iljaycees&amp;amp;sa=D&amp;amp;sntz=1&amp;amp;usg=AFQjCNHf7VL-KhmodulCK_eIa7OQSTI6Jw&#34;&gt;/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.google.com/url?q=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.globalproblems-globalsolutions.org%2Fgoto%2F2011iljaycees&amp;amp;sa=D&amp;amp;sntz=1&amp;amp;usg=AFQjCNHf7VL-KhmodulCK_eIa7OQSTI6Jw&#34;&gt;goto&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.google.com/url?q=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.globalproblems-globalsolutions.org%2Fgoto%2F2011iljaycees&amp;amp;sa=D&amp;amp;sntz=1&amp;amp;usg=AFQjCNHf7VL-KhmodulCK_eIa7OQSTI6Jw&#34;&gt;/2011&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.google.com/url?q=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.globalproblems-globalsolutions.org%2Fgoto%2F2011iljaycees&amp;amp;sa=D&amp;amp;sntz=1&amp;amp;usg=AFQjCNHf7VL-KhmodulCK_eIa7OQSTI6Jw&#34;&gt;iljaycees&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:black;&#34;&gt; and if you have any questions or comments about my article feel free to email me at &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:Richard.Lewis@iljaycees.org&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:blue;text-decoration:underline;&#34;&gt;Richard&lt;a href=&#34;mailto:Richard.Lewis@iljaycees.org&#34;&gt;.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;mailto:Richard.Lewis@iljaycees.org&#34;&gt;Lewis&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;mailto:Richard.Lewis@iljaycees.org&#34;&gt;@&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;mailto:Richard.Lewis@iljaycees.org&#34;&gt;iljaycees&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;mailto:Richard.Lewis@iljaycees.org&#34;&gt;.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;mailto:Richard.Lewis@iljaycees.org&#34;&gt;org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:black;&#34;&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to spend 10 dollars</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2011-02-11-how-to-spend-10-dollars/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2011 10:03:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2011-02-11-how-to-spend-10-dollars/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Last month in my Illinois Jaycees newsletter article I talked about what you could do with 10 dollars and the Nothing But Nets Program. How cool is this, today I came across a you tube video asking the same question. The point of the matter is for 10 dollars you can save a person from malaria. Get involved in the Nothing But Nets campaign it can prevent the spread of a disease.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Top Ten WordPress Plugins</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2011-01-29-my-top-ten-wordpress-plugins/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jan 2011 17:59:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2011-01-29-my-top-ten-wordpress-plugins/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hey so I thought it was time to put out another top ten list and what better topic then WordPress !!!!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://wordpress.org/extend/plugins/akismet/&#34;&gt;Akismet&lt;/a&gt; The best dam comment spam filter out there.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://wordpress.org/extend/plugins/simple-social-sharing-widgets-icons/&#34;&gt;Simple Social – Sharing Widgets &amp;amp; Icons&lt;/a&gt; This is a great little plug in it allows you simple integration with basically any social network out there.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.boloxe.com/techblog/&#34;&gt;kPicasa Gallery&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:black;&#34;&gt; I found this plugin last month it makes it easy to integration a Picasa album into your website quickly&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://ace.dev.rain.hu/&#34;&gt;Advanced Category Excluder&lt;/a&gt; OMG this is one of my favorite it allows you filter out post from your homepage or archives by category or tag.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://urbangiraffe.com/plugins/redirection/&#34;&gt;Redirection&lt;/a&gt; Yeah so I sent out some links a while back and then changed the post locations this little plugin allows for you redirect those posts to their new homes.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://wordpress.org/extend/plugins/google-analytics-for-wordpress/&#34;&gt;Google Analytics for WordPress&lt;/a&gt; This is a great little plugin that allows for better integration with Google Analytics&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://crowdfavorite.com/wordpress/plugins/twitter-tools/&#34;&gt;Twitter Tools&lt;/a&gt; This a massive plug-in that bring a couple key integration features&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://wordpress.org/extend/plugins/xbox-gamertag-widget/&#34;&gt;XBOX Live Gamertag&lt;/a&gt; This plugin is just a widget that displays my xbox 360 gamercard on my website.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.wesg.ca/2008/08/wordpress-widget-most-popular/&#34;&gt;Most Popular Posts&lt;/a&gt; Just a simple little widget that displays my most popular on the sidebar&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.socialprofilr.com/&#34;&gt;Social Profilr&lt;/a&gt; This plugin is just a widget that displays icon links to all my social network profiles on my website.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So there you go my top ten plugins for WordPress hopefully you find this post useful. If you’ve got some favorites I’d love to read about them so just leave me a comment.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Making Our Impact with Nothing But Net</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2011-01-24-making-our-impact-with-nothing-but-net/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2011 11:14:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2011-01-24-making-our-impact-with-nothing-but-net/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;What can you do with 10 dollars? Hmmm buy a shirt, buy 2 footlong subs at subway, buy a couple gallons of gas, 2 cups of Grande coffee at starbucks, or save a life. Yup it’s true for just 10 dollars you can save a life. Malaria infects nearly 500 million&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.gogorichie.com/wp-content/uploads/2011/01/012411_1714_MakingOurIm1.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt; people each year and kills more than one million of those who become infected. Last year State Chairwomen Sue Warmuskerken introduced us to the JCI Nothing But Nets program and with yours along with all the members of JCI efforts we have made an impact on this disease. It use to be every 30 seconds a kid was dying from Malaria. Since our participation in JCI Nothing but Nets, it is down to a kid dying every 45 seconds. Now that’s a impact, but I think we can increase that impact this year. Now if you’re not familiar with this program let give you a quick overview. The program is run by the UN and JCI our international organization is a partner in helping the fight. But of course their not along tons of major sports teams, fortune 500 companies and other non for profit groups are helping too. The way it works is for every 10 dollars donated a bed net is manufactured and given to person in need within Africa. Malaria carrying mosquitoes generally bite between 10:00 p.m. and 4:00 a.m. A bed net is typically hung above the center of a bed or sleeping space so that it completely covers the sleeping person. One bed net can safely last a family for about three years, thanks to a long-lasting insecticide woven into the net fabric. This year our goal is to STEP UP double the funds raised across the state in 2010 and to provide 300 nets. Visit the Illinois Jaycees 2011 team’s website to get involved &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.globalproblems-globalsolutions.org/goto/2011iljaycees&#34;&gt;http://www.globalproblems-globalsolutions.org/goto/2011iljaycees&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Allow For Me To Reintroduce Myself</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2011-01-24-allow-for-me-to-reintroduce-myself/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2011 09:45:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2011-01-24-allow-for-me-to-reintroduce-myself/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-family:Arial;font-size:9pt;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:#000000;&#34;&gt;This year I’ll be serving as the Illinois Jaycees 2011 National Programs / Government Involvement State Chairmen or NPGI State Chair for short also I’ll be serving as the North Region Treasurer oh and also the Website Program Manager for the US Jaycees once again. The goal this year is promote the programs The US Jaycees and JCI have established to all of our chapters across the state. The Jaycees have a have long history of bring fourth change throughout the nation with programs like Get Out to Vote and other Government Involvement programs, Outstanding Young Farmers, Support Our Troops, Distinguish Service Award which became the Ten Outstanding Young Americans, Relay for life and just added in 2009 Riley’s Toys. These programs really bring home our last line of our creed &lt;em&gt;“service to humanity is the best work of life”.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Support Camp New Hope</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2011-01-12-support-camp-new-hope/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2011 11:55:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2011-01-12-support-camp-new-hope/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.myfavoritecamp.org/index.html&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https:///www.myfavoritecamp.org/images/cnhfirst.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Each year members of the Illinois Jaycees support Camp New Hope through various community drives and as part of our annual fund raising campaign. Camp New Hope Respite building started construction 10 years ago, but due to the loss of State and Federal funding and the despair of our current economy, the construction remains unfinished. This building is used for the year round respite program which gives reprive to those families with members with special needs. Vote to give this idea 25K: Finish Camp New Hope Respite Building for the developmentally disabled &lt;a href=&#34;http://pep.si/fZ5MDa&#34;&gt;http://pep.si/fZ5MDa&lt;/a&gt; and you can learn more about and support them through their website at &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.myfavoritecamp.org/&#34;&gt;http://www.myfavoritecamp.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>T-SQL Tuesday 13: Interacting With The Business</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/sql/interacting-with-the-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/sql/interacting-with-the-business/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://gogorichiesitefiles.blob.core.windows.net/publicfiles/tsqltuesday.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;T-SQL Tusday&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I come from a different world in my company, I’m not IT though I have formal training, I speak the lingo, and wear the uniform of Jeans, t-shirt, glasses and ton’s of geekieness in my swagger. I’m what they call &lt;a href=&#34;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Business_intelligence&#34;&gt;Business Intelligence&lt;/a&gt; or better known as Shadow IT.  Though i&amp;rsquo;m up front about what we do and the impact it has. In my company I’m the middle person between what the business thinks it wants and what it really needs long term. Most of time what they really want is a short term solution. You know something quick and dirty to fix the bleeding of money and correct behavior.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing The New Mount Prospect Jaycees Website</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2010-12-10-introducing-the-new-mount-prospect-jaycees-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2010 15:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2010-12-10-introducing-the-new-mount-prospect-jaycees-website/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.gogorichie.com/wp-content/uploads/2011/07/10_12_10_10_46_30.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.gogorichie.com/wp-content/uploads/2011/07/10_12_10_10_46_30_thumb.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Mount Prospect Jaycees 2010&#34; title=&#34;Mount Prospect Jaycees 2010&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When the Mount Prospect Jaycees needed a update to their aging website which i first built back in &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.gogorichie.com/2008/11/mount-prospect-jaycees-site-comments/&#34;&gt;2008&lt;/a&gt;. I worked with the chapter executive board to bring a fresh new look to their website. For this site it required moving over all the current chapter contain as well as introducing some new features. I choose &lt;a href=&#34;http://wordpress.org/&#34;&gt;WordPress&lt;/a&gt; as the platform to host their site because two of their board members were familiar with it and training the rest of the board wouldn’t be a problem. Also sent just about two hour training the sites webmaster and off she was running making updates and changes on her own. The Mount Prospect Jaycees is a leadership development and networking group for adults between the age of 18 and 40 in Mount Prospect, Illinois. Check out the groups website at &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.MountProspectjaycees.org&#34;&gt;http://www.MountProspectjaycees.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grooving to the beats with Grooveshark</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2010-12-10-grooving-to-the-beats-with-grooveshark/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2010 10:41:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2010-12-10-grooving-to-the-beats-with-grooveshark/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;So only my old AIM friends would get that title. But just last week &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.grooveshark.com&#34;&gt;grooveshark.com&lt;/a&gt; went through a full revamp of their website, switching from a flash based website to the new internet language of html5. Which seems to quickly becoming the standard. I’m excited about the switch for two reasons. First technically you can you use the site now on your iPad and iPhone in the near future. I’ve tried it on my iPad the other night and i got a notice saying my computer was not running flash and asked if i want to continue. Second you memory footprint used by the site will be significantly smaller. Check out the new site layout below in the picture and try it for yourself.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Things to make my life easier</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2010-11-30-things-to-make-my-life-easier/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2010 15:23:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2010-11-30-things-to-make-my-life-easier/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I thought it was time to put together a little list of my favorite computer things i use to make my life easier. No big deal just the things i use everyday no matter if I’m at work or at home. I find myself using these products all the time.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Hope you enjoy my list and post comments and share your thoughts&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.Evernote.com&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https:///cultureslurp.com/wp-content/uploads/2009/10/grooveshark-search.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1)&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.Evernote.com&#34;&gt;Evernote&lt;/a&gt; – I first found the app for my the iPad before i knew about the website. But it’s be came one of my favorites and there’s a desktop version and one for my blackberry too.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using DateDiff to Control Content</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/sql/using-datediff-to-control-content/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/sql/using-datediff-to-control-content/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Last Friday I got a data request from a group asking for a report to be generated bi-hourly for customer request that were not responded to in a time span of two hours. So looking at the data I noticed that there were two columns that were time stamped one when the request was submitted and another when the request was completed, so this was easy I filtered out where the completed data was null and wrote a where statement using a Datediff syntax to breakdown the input date time stamp by hour and then subtracting two so my sql statement looks like the following example.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Favorite Business Intelligence Blogs</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/sql/favorite-business-intelligence-blogs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/sql/favorite-business-intelligence-blogs/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As I start to dive deeper into the Business Intelligence area I&amp;rsquo;ve started putting together a list of my favorite blogs covering this area, in no particular order.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.bidn.com/&#34;&gt;http://www.bidn.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://sqlbi.blogspot.com/&#34;&gt;http://sqlbi.blogspot.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://cwebbbi.spaces.live.com/&#34;&gt;http://cwebbbi.spaces.live.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://denglishbi.spaces.live.com/&#34;&gt;http://denglishbi.spaces.live.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://bi-polar23.blogspot.com/&#34;&gt;http://bi-polar23.blogspot.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://sqlserverbiblog.com/&#34;&gt;http://sqlserverbiblog.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://shahfaisalmuhammed.wordpress.com/&#34;&gt;http://shahfaisalmuhammed.wordpress.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://tomislavpiasevoli.spaces.live.com/default.aspx&#34;&gt;http://tomislavpiasevoli.spaces.live.com/default.aspx&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://bimatters.spaces.live.com/&#34;&gt;http://bimatters.spaces.live.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SSIS Reference Points</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/sql/ssis-reference-points/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/sql/ssis-reference-points/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- ![](http://farm4.static.flickr.com/3393/3429634150_3deb0b5b10.jpg) --&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is a shout out to my former team member learning about SSIS packages for the first time and getting ready to move from SQL 2000 to SQL 2008. Here’s some good reference points for how to do the basics.   Now before you call me and ask what does SSIS stands it stands for &lt;a href=&#34;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/SQL_Server_Integration_Services&#34;&gt;SQL Server Integration Services&lt;/a&gt;. So below is a couple links that i found i think you may find helpful in your new adventure.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virtual Meetings For Free</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2010-09-30-virtual-meetings-for-free/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2010 17:20:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2010-09-30-virtual-meetings-for-free/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.gogorichie.com/wp-content/uploads/2010/09/image.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.gogorichie.com/wp-content/uploads/2010/09/image_thumb.png&#34; alt=&#34;image&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You every want to plan a project or host a committee meeting virtually but don’t have a conference call &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.gogorichie.com/wp-content/uploads/2010/09/image1.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.gogorichie.com/wp-content/uploads/2010/09/image_thumb1.png&#34; alt=&#34;image&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;number of your own or know where to start? Well your in luck thanks to a little company called Dimdim you can now host online meetings, trainings, and brainstorming sessions from the comfort of your own home for free. Dimdim is a software company that provides a web-based platform for real-time, rich-media collaboration and meetings. Dimdim provides free web conferencing service where users can share desktops, show slides, collaborate, chat, talk and broadcast via webcam. Dimdim was recognized in 2009 as a up and coming startup and received many awards over the years. Dimdim is free for meetings under 20 people and only 25 dollars month for meetings larger then 20 but with that extra cost you get tons of premium features such ask online meeting logging meeting attends automatically and recording of the meeting and online signups of the meetings. Which comes in handy for tracking who attended your training and allowing for people to sign up for it up for them online. Dimdim is a awesome product i found out about from Kevin Rose and it comes in handy so often. if you have questions about it let me know and i would love to tell you more about it.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Documenting Isn’t That Hard</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2010-09-30-documenting-isnt-that-hard/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2010 16:52:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2010-09-30-documenting-isnt-that-hard/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Just like the title said it’s not that hard and it one of the most important things in software and process &lt;img src=&#34;https://blog.makezine.com/upload/2009/03/recent_makers_notebook_hacks/fridgeNotebookHack.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;fridgeNotebookHack.jpg&#34;&gt;development is the the Documentation part. But it’s most often the most over looked do to time and no short term benefit. But long term after the developer has forgotten what they did back then the documentation they have written will still be there for the next developer to come along and revise, enhance, or just get a better understanding of what is taking place and how it done. Below are a couple of things everyone should remember when documenting.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Twitter &amp; The North Region Jaycees</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2010-08-23-twitter-the-north-region-jaycees/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2010 08:20:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2010-08-23-twitter-the-north-region-jaycees/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https:///docs.google.com/File?id=df7fzjds_13d2mj9vcr_b&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;What are you doing? that’s a question that you are probably asked dozens of time a day. How many of you use the Facebook status function each day? How many of you use it more than once each day? Well, this year the North Region Jaycees are trying something new and we will be using a free service named Twitter to communicate all kinds of one line answers, event postings, random thoughts, and newsflashes about articles recently added to the Region’s website &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.northregionjaycees.com/&#34;&gt;&lt;u&gt;www.northregionjaycees.com&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. How can you and your chapter use Twitter? Twitter has many uses such as sending out help requests to all your members while you are already on site project day via a single text message from your cell phone. It could also be used for sending updates to your chapter website and my favorite- keeping members up-to-date with upcoming events. Once they read how much fun you are having, they may want to attend the next time-especially state and national conventions. Twitter’s popularity has exploded over the last year thanks in part to the 2008 Presidential race. Both parties used Twitter to communicate with hundreds of thousands of supporters. Last year, Dell showed that Twitter can be used as a source of income when they generated over a million dollars in sales from the service by posting items for sale.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stupid Duplicates</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/sql/stupid-duplicates/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jul 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/sql/stupid-duplicates/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;So the other day my former team member call me asking for help. She had inserted the same data into a table three or more times and needed to get rid of them. For those of you with duplications and need to delete them here’s a little statement i came up with and gave her.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;DELETE FROM TBL_Employees&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;WHERE     (EmpID IN&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;                          (SELECT     MAX(EmpID) AS Expr2&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;                            FROM          TBL_Employees&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;                            GROUP BY FirstName&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 degrees in 365 days</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2010-06-19-10-degrees-in-365-days/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jun 2010 07:59:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2010-06-19-10-degrees-in-365-days/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Each year being in the Jaycees brings something exciting to do and well 2010 is no different. This year in addition to serving on my state’s board and the US Jaycees board I’ve decided to create my own personal challenge for myself. That is to be come a tenth degree Jaycee in the course of the year. The degree program is designed to build great leaders. It starts off at with the basics getting a person socially involved to develop the social and networking skills and then progress over time to the point of where the person is heading up committees, chapter, districts, and states. Most of the things identified in the degrees program I’ve done of the last three years but where I come from we didn’t participate in the degree program and we produce great leaders still.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Determing SQL Server Table Size Tip</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/sql/determing-sql-server-table-size-tip/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/sql/determing-sql-server-table-size-tip/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;From time to time i run into problems of where some new table appears on m  server and starts eating up all my space. Well i came across this blog posting a while back that does a great job of explaining how to determine the table sizes in a database in SQL 2000 it works in 2005 too.  check it out and let me know what you think.  &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.mitchelsellers.com/blogs/articletype/articleview/articleid/121/determing-sql-server-table-size.aspx&#34;&gt;http://www.mitchelsellers.com/blogs/articletype/articleview/articleid/121/determing-sql-server-table-size.aspx&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SQL Saturday 31 Wrapup</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/sql/sql-saturday-31-wrapup/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/sql/sql-saturday-31-wrapup/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://gogorichiesitefiles.blob.core.windows.net/publicfiles/sql_saturday_logo.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://gogorichiesitefiles.blob.core.windows.net/publicfiles/sqlsat31/87820832.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;In Wes Dumey building a data warehouse session&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Earlier this month i attended my first SQL meetup called &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.sqlsaturday.com/31/eventhome.aspx&#34;&gt;SQL Saturday #31&lt;/a&gt; i&amp;rsquo;m not sure why it&amp;rsquo;s numbered  31 cause i realized they don&amp;rsquo;t go in order. But yeah so it was hosted in Elk Grove so it wasn&amp;rsquo;t to far away. I knew it was going to be a awesome day when i met this guy in the registration line who reads my site and learned a couple SQL tricks from it. How sweet is that right? So SQL Saturday is put on by the Professional Association for SQL Server and ran by volunteers.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Date Formatting In SQL</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/sql/date-formatting-in-sql/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/sql/date-formatting-in-sql/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- ![image](http://www.gogorichie.com/wp-content/uploads/2010/03/image_thumb2.png &#34;image&#34;)(http://www.gogorichie.com/wp-content/uploads/2010/03/image2.png) --&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I got a request for a report the other day so I built this massive 90 line SQL statement to pull all the data requested. So I sent off a copy of the data report and the guy tells me that he needs the date formatted (YYYYMMDD) instead of (YYYY-MM-DD-HHMMSS) and then he was like is that going to be a problem and I was like ha not really. Give me a moment and I&amp;rsquo;ll send you a simple. Since I can’t remember the correct expression I did a quick Google search and came across this awesome page &lt;a href=&#34;http://anubhavg.wordpress.com/2009/06/11/how-to-format-datetime-date-in-sql-server-2005/&#34; title=&#34;http://anubhavg.wordpress.com/2009/06/11/how-to-format-datetime-date-in-sql-server-2005/&#34;&gt;http://anubhavg.wordpress.com/2009/06/11/how-to-format-datetime-date-in-sql-server-2005/&lt;/a&gt; covering exactly what I was looking for.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 2nd Online Training Announced</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2010-03-09-the-2nd-online-training-announced/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2010 08:53:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2010-03-09-the-2nd-online-training-announced/</guid>
      <description>&lt;table&gt;&#xA;  &lt;thead&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;th&gt;The next online training will be on Monday the 15th. We will be learning about how to make on online survey and taking a look at three products in the market all of which are free. We will also learn how to build a survey using the Google Docs platform. Training is open to the first 50 people with 33 seats allocated to the state staff. Sign up for the training using the widget on the right side.&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;          &lt;th&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://widgets.clearspring.com/o/499d781e7a2ff8ce/4b965c363e647208/49a40d8b9c8624f5/3b09127f/-cpid/54f914fa14e9687d/showRecording/false/showTimer/false/showTranscript/false/showRegistration/false&#34;&gt;http://widgets.clearspring.com/o/499d781e7a2ff8ce/4b965c363e647208/49a40d8b9c8624f5/3b09127f/-cpid/54f914fa14e9687d/showRecording/false/showTimer/false/showTranscript/false/showRegistration/false&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/thead&gt;&#xA;  &lt;tbody&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/tbody&gt;&#xA;&lt;/table&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing The New Hoffman Estates Jaycees Website</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2010-02-28-introducing-the-new-hoffman-estates-jaycees-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2010 07:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2010-02-28-introducing-the-new-hoffman-estates-jaycees-website/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;When the Hoffman Estates Jaycees needed a update to their aging website. I worked with the chapter executive board to bring a fresh new look to their website. For this site it required moving over all the current chapter contain as well as introducing some new features. I choose &lt;a href=&#34;http://wordpress.org/&#34;&gt;WordPress&lt;/a&gt; as the platform to host their site because two of their board members were familiar with it and training the rest of the board wouldn’t be a problem. The Hoffman Estates Jaycees is a leadership development and networking group for adults between the age of 18 and 40 in Hoffman Estates, Illinois. Check out the groups website at &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.hoffmanestatesjaycees.org&#34;&gt;http://www.hoffmanestatesjaycees.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Social Network Integration</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2010-02-12-social-network-integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2010 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2010-02-12-social-network-integration/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Integrating into social networks is just important as being on them in the&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.gogorichie.com/wp-content/uploads/2010/03/image1.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.gogorichie.com/wp-content/uploads/2010/03/image_thumb1.png&#34; alt=&#34;image&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt; past the &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.usjaycees.org/&#34;&gt;US Jaycees website&lt;/a&gt; hasn’t made reference to our involvement with the online social networks. Today I introduced a new module called &lt;a href=&#34;http://extensions.joomla.org/extensions/social-web/social-profiles/5438&#34;&gt;stalker&lt;/a&gt; which allows us to promote our social network pages on our homepage as well as I wrote a custom module for displaying the organizations &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.facebook.com/TheUnitedStatesJuniorChamber&#34;&gt;Facebook fan page&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Business As Usual</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2010-02-02-business-as-usual/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2010 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2010-02-02-business-as-usual/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Today I’ll begin working the US Jaycees Site. My first task is to perform a Full DB backup just incase something goes wrong. This was going well until I ran into my first problem i was unable to access the db server which is no big deal since i could get into the php admin panel. It’s been so long since I’ve had to perform a manual backup in MYSQL. But that what they make Google for right? After getting the backup completed and burned to a CD i moved on to updated the directory and posting some new documents. While doing this I came up with a interesting idea to keep track of my work though out the year. I’m using Google docs and created a form using the form feature to track my work which is pictured below. I really haven’t put much though into changing the site design and layout. I personally like it so lets see what people ask me to do. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.gogorichie.com/wp-content/uploads/2010/03/image.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.gogorichie.com/wp-content/uploads/2010/03/image_thumb.png&#34; alt=&#34;image&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guess Who Updating the site</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2010-01-29-guess-who-updating-the-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2010 08:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2010-01-29-guess-who-updating-the-site/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It’s me !!!!!it was just recently announced that I’ll be taking the US Jaycees website from the current webmaster David. No real reason why was giving why the change. But they posted they were looking on the site and I responded with a letter to President Jeff and the Exec board. Look for more postings over the 12 months about my adventures as their 2010 Website Program Manager.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Fav 5 Windows Home Server Add-ins</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2009-11-12-my-fav-5-windows-home-server-add-ins/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2009 07:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2009-11-12-my-fav-5-windows-home-server-add-ins/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The other day I was talking with a friend about my Windows Home Server configuration and thought I would post a little something about what addins I’m running or as the the title said my Fav 5. I like to keep my WHS&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.gogorichie.com/wp-content/uploads/2009/11/image1.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.gogorichie.com/wp-content/uploads/2009/11/image_thumb1.png&#34; alt=&#34;image&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt; running light and simple so the addins I like to use take advantage of features already built into windows 2003 and don’t put any extra strain on the server. But I still like to play around from time to time with some extra stuff.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The day after the 120 days are up</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2009-11-01-the-day-after-the-120-days-are-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2009 09:29:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2009-11-01-the-day-after-the-120-days-are-up/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https:///www.electricdeal.com/images/items/8938.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;First let me start by saying Microsoft allows you to download any of there new operating systems for trial period usually 120 days but some are 90. My 120 day trial period for windows home server ended on September 15th. I waited all the way to 121&lt;sup&gt;st&lt;/sup&gt; day to upgrade even though I knew by the 90&lt;sup&gt;th&lt;/sup&gt; day I was planning on buying it. So when I finally got around to getting a licensed copy, which I actually ended up getting it for my birthday. Now if your unfamiliar with Windows Home Server it’s basically the stay at home server and monitors all your houses computers for issues and backs them up just in case something happens and it feeds media to our TV’s and PC. You don’t need to have advanced skills to use it. Just set it up and forget about it will take care of you. So after sending the last 120 days getting to know the Home Server product. So here ***&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.gogorichie.com/wp-content/uploads/2009/11/image.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.gogorichie.com/wp-content/uploads/2009/11/image_thumb.png&#34; alt=&#34;image&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;***what I learned &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;first&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; 512MB of Ram is good start but if your going to use addin’s your going to need a little more I didn’t go all crazy, I doubled the memory and now I’m getting great results. &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Second&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; configuring remote access on Comcast is easier then think. you just need to configure the right ports and your done. &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Third&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; there’s a addin out called WHIIST it’s the greatest thing basically what it does is builds on the the built-in IIS and remote access feature and allows for you host other site as well as customize your own remote access site. The &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;fourth&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; thing I learned and this wasn’t until the end was be very care how you reinstall&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.gogorichie.com/wp-content/uploads/2009/11/shares.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.gogorichie.com/wp-content/uploads/2009/11/shares_thumb.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;shares&#34; title=&#34;shares&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt; your plug ins once you decide to buy the full version. I ran into problems when I reinstalled all my plug ins at once. I turned to We Got Served for help cause I could any information about my issue on the Microsoft forum. Which leads me to my &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;fifth&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; thing I learned The support community outside Microsoft is far better then the one provided them. This product is truly led by it’s enthusiast of course the tops one work for Microsoft or are recognized by them as MVP’s. The community is so supported that even Microsoft points users to theses community sites for news about recently developed addin’s and other product information. Now my biggest beef with product isn’t even the product its the fact that Dell doesn’t have a product out there currently that is built around Windows Home Server I freaking A your getting killed by HP, Acer, and mine others. By the ways what the point of having your own blog with followers if you can’t poke fun at others stupid Dell get with the times.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The First 5 Things I do When I Get a New BlackBerry</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2009-08-17-the-first-5-things-i-do-when-i-get-a-new-blackberry/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2009 16:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2009-08-17-the-first-5-things-i-do-when-i-get-a-new-blackberry/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Last week i got the new &lt;a href=&#34;http://na.blackberry.com/eng/devices/blackberrycurve8500/&#34;&gt;Blackberry 8520 Curve&lt;/a&gt; and i though I would write my first five things similar to ones did on the &lt;a href=&#34;http://blogs.blackberry.com/2009/07/the-first-5-things---andrey.html&#34;&gt;blackberry blog site&lt;/a&gt;. Since i this my third blackberry I’ve got my steps setting up down pretty good.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.gogorichie.com/wp-content/uploads/2009/08/image.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.gogorichie.com/wp-content/uploads/2009/08/image_thumb.png&#34; alt=&#34;image&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Download &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.google.com/mobile/&#34;&gt;Google Mobile Apps&lt;/a&gt;; OMG this has got to be my used applications on my blackberry. First the Google sync is one hell of an application it syncs up my address book and calendar to my Gmail account. Then instead of using the blackberry maps application i would rather use Google maps. Google&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Download &lt;a href=&#34;http://na.blackberry.com/eng/devices/features/social/facebook.jsp&#34;&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt; and setup app so that it downloads pictures to my contacts, calendar events, and what not’s&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Pull down a new service book; so that my work, Jaycees, and personal emails start flowing to my new device.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Ping all my friends with my new pin; Blackberry messenger has to be one of most easy to use messenger clients out there, btw if you want my PIN text me and I’ll give it to you.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Set my background; of course i use one the White Sox. I pulled one that i took last year while me and Ann was at the sox game down from my Facebook mobile pictures album.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This new Blackberry device has way more capabilities then my last model. First I’m taking full advantage of the &lt;a href=&#34;http://na.blackberry.com/eng/services/appworld/?iid=AppWorld_Homepage&#34;&gt;Apps World&lt;/a&gt; and second OMG &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.pandora.com/blackberry&#34;&gt;Pandora&lt;/a&gt; runs so smooth and fast on it just like playing a song from my iTunes Library.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why i tweet</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2009-05-08-why-i-tweet/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2009 12:11:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2009-05-08-why-i-tweet/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://twitter.com/gogorichie/statuses/1733740088&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.gogorichie.com/wp-content/uploads/2009/05/image.png&#34; alt=&#34;image&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I’m a really big fan of micro-Blog services for a couple reasons one I hate writing long blog &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.gogorichie.com/wp-content/uploads/2009/05/image1.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.gogorichie.com/wp-content/uploads/2009/05/image-thumb.png&#34; alt=&#34;image&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;postings and the other is just the simplicity of the technology I can just post to it with one hand while driving or while eating, or sitting in a meeting. Since&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.gogorichie.com/wp-content/uploads/2009/05/image2.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.gogorichie.com/wp-content/uploads/2009/05/image-thumb1.png&#34; alt=&#34;image&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt; I begin twittering just about three months ago I’ve posted over 600 updates. Everything from my daily status to just random questions, but hey so check out my stats below of my usage patterns.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Changing the default My documents</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2009-04-13-changing-the-default-my-documents/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2009 13:05:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2009-04-13-changing-the-default-my-documents/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.gogorichie.com/wp-content/uploads/2009/04/image3.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.gogorichie.com/wp-content/uploads/2009/04/windowslivewriter88b32ebe8110-d7e3image-thumb.png&#34; alt=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;I’m one of those weird people who use multiple computers each day to get work things done. When I’m in the office I use my desktop PC and then at home I use my work laptop, prior to last year accessing my work files on my Desktop from work was nearly impossible. An then everyone got their own personal network share about year. Since then I’ve been saving all my files to my share and accessing them their over our corp. vpn to get to them. Well &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.gogorichie.com/wp-content/uploads/2009/04/windowslivewriter88b32ebe8110-d7e3image-4.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.gogorichie.com/wp-content/uploads/2009/04/windowslivewriter88b32ebe8110-d7e3image-thumb-1.png&#34; alt=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt; each time when I start a new file I had to change my saving location from my documents to my network folder and well, that gets kind of old so I figure why not take it one step further. Why don’t I just change my default my documents location. Well after downing a little search on the Internet I came a article in the MSDN Here’s a link to it if you want to change your default my documents location too &lt;a href=&#34;http://tinyurl.com/9ngo7y&#34;&gt;http://tinyurl.com/9ngo7y&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why I Relay 4 Life</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2009-04-11-why-i-relay-4-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Apr 2009 18:21:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2009-04-11-why-i-relay-4-life/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.gogorichie.com/wp-content/uploads/2009/04/image2.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.gogorichie.com/wp-content/uploads/2009/04/image-thumb2.png&#34; alt=&#34;image&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt; My primary reason for support relay for life is as you may or may not know I lost my grand father to his battle with cancer a few years back and followed by two aunts a few months later. That made really think about cancer and we can cure it. Cancer is one of those diseases that effects people no matter if their rich or poor . If their Black or white, we all know someone who has been impacted by cancer. For the past three years I’ve gotten involved with Relays all across the northwest suburbs. As you may &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.gogorichie.com/wp-content/uploads/2009/04/s73009281.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.gogorichie.com/wp-content/uploads/2009/04/s73009281-thumb.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Me &amp;amp; Ann with the MP JC&amp;rsquo;s&#34; title=&#34;Me &amp;amp; Ann with the MP JC&#39;s&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;know I’m a member of the &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.usjaycees.org/index.php?option=com_content&amp;amp;task=view&amp;amp;id=78&amp;amp;Itemid=204&#34;&gt;Jaycees&lt;/a&gt; and they are heavy supporters of the American Cancer Society, especially the Relay For Life program. Please consider making a donation to the American Cancer Society to keep the fight going for those we’ve lost in the battle of cancer.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spring Consolidation</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2009-04-11-spring-consolidation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Apr 2009 14:15:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2009-04-11-spring-consolidation/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.gogorichie.com/wp-content/uploads/2009/04/image.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.gogorichie.com/wp-content/uploads/2009/04/image-thumb.png&#34; alt=&#34;image&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt; Ahh it’s the most wonderful time of the year, the sun is shining the grass is growing nice and green. It couldn’t be more picture perfect. I’m just relaxing at home outside with a miller lite and my laptop. I figure today was a great day to spend a little time cleaning up my network. My home is scanning for duplicate files&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.gogorichie.com/wp-content/uploads/2009/04/image1.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.gogorichie.com/wp-content/uploads/2009/04/image-thumb1.png&#34; alt=&#34;image&#34; title=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt; across my network and when it’s done it will be time to dump some of those too. I figure now is a good time while I wait why don’t I import some more postings from back in the day when I use to have a livejournal account. Today I’m introducing just about 200 new posting from 2005 and 2006 and few from early 2008 that were posted to my old livejournal blog “&lt;a href=&#34;http://gogorichie.livejournal.com&#34;&gt;The Wondering Mind Of GoGoRichie&lt;/a&gt;” I hope you enjoy them there quiet funny especial the ones written after coming home from the bar such as “&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.gogorichie.com/?p=599&#34;&gt;How to block the mother hen attack&lt;/a&gt;” I know it’s one Jessica’s favorites.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to find duplicate rows in SQL Server</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/sql/how-to-find-duplicate-rows-in-sql-server/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/microsoft/sql/how-to-find-duplicate-rows-in-sql-server/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I ran into this problem the other day at work with duplicate rows while trying to merge data from two separate tables into the same table. I couldn&amp;rsquo;t remember so I just ran a quick search using &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.google.com/search?hl=en&amp;amp;q=duplicate+records+in+sql&#34;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; and came across the solution on a &lt;a href=&#34;http://support.microsoft.com/kb/139444&#34;&gt;Microsoft knowledge base&lt;/a&gt; page.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;-------------------------------------------------------&lt;/pre&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;**_The first step is to identify which rows have duplicate primary key&#xD;&#xA;values:_**&lt;/pre&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;SELECT col1, col2, count(*)FROM t1GROUP BY col1, col2HAVING count(*) &gt; 1&lt;/pre&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;**_This will return one row for each set of duplicate PK values&#xD;&#xA;in the table. The last column in this result is the number of&#xD;&#xA;duplicates for the particular PK value._**&lt;/pre&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;col1               col2&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Happy Birthday Gogorichie.com</title>
      <link>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2005-07-03-14127/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2005 20:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.gogorichie.com/blog/archieve/2005-07-03-14127/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;On July 9th 2002 Gogorichie.com was born. Here are some stats recorded during the last year.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;3,318 unique visitors came to the site, as determined by typical behavior of browsers with a non-rotating IP address and including a projection of the true number of visitors with rotating IP addresses.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The web site received 5,693 visits. A typical visitor examined 17.19 distinct files before leaving the site. A typical visit lasted for 6.49 minutes. The longest visit lasted for 938 minutes.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
