<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>microsoft on I&#39;m Richard Lewis</title>
    <link>http://www.gogorichie.com/tags/microsoft/</link>
    <description>Recent content in microsoft on I&#39;m Richard Lewis</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2019 23:53:00 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://www.gogorichie.com/tags/microsoft/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>My Favorite VSCode Plugins Of 2019</title>
      <link>http://www.gogorichie.com/posts/2019_fav_vscode_plugins/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2019 23:53:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gogorichie.com/posts/2019_fav_vscode_plugins/</guid>
      <description>2019 was a big year for me using VS Code before the beginning of the year I was still using Notepad++ along with Visual Studio as my daily IDE&amp;rsquo;s. But in January I tried to use VS Code every day for 30 days and I haven&amp;rsquo;t stopped and along the way, I also convinced a few of my Co-workers to convert over as well. I remember reading the 2018 Stack Overflow release their annual Developer survey results last December, one of the interesting things that I noticed was that VS Code had risen to the top as the Most Popular Development Environment among Developers and Admins with 35% of 75,398 respondents claiming to use it which is pretty cool for a tool-less than 5 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>April Meme 15 Assignment</title>
      <link>http://www.gogorichie.com/posts/sql/april-meme15-assignment/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gogorichie.com/posts/sql/april-meme15-assignment/</guid>
      <description>Another #Meme 15 topic brought you by MVP Jason Strate (blog | twitter). This month topic &amp;ldquo;What are ten blogs that you think other SQL Server professionals should be following but might not be?&amp;quot; Coming up with a list of just 10 is harder than I thought narrowing it down to ten is just way to hard but i was able to do. The list I put together covers everyone from the newbie to SQL to the all-round DBA.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
