<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>JCI on I&#39;m Richard Lewis</title>
    <link>http://www.gogorichie.com/tags/jci/</link>
    <description>Recent content in JCI on I&#39;m Richard Lewis</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 15:43:51 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://www.gogorichie.com/tags/jci/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Why I Jaycee</title>
      <link>http://www.gogorichie.com/posts/jci/why_i_jaycee/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 15:43:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gogorichie.com/posts/jci/why_i_jaycee/</guid>
      <description>The second week of October annually is Jaycee Week, it&amp;rsquo;s the week where we as Jaycees celebrate the founding of our organization in 1915 by Henry Giessenbier Jr. Ironically this month marks my 14th year as a member. So what better time of the year than now to share with you why I Jaycee? I joined the Jaycees to help make my community a better place. But I stay a Jaycee because it gives me the opportunity to be a Young Active Citizen, who can create positive change within my community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Four Component Approach</title>
      <link>http://www.gogorichie.com/posts/jci/the-four-component-approach/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gogorichie.com/posts/jci/the-four-component-approach/</guid>
      <description>The Jaycees as you all know by now is more than just a community service organization. Since the founding in 1915 it has held true to its primary purpose of building young leaders to tackle the challenges of tomorrow. In 2013 I will be servicing you as your State Membership Development vice President; the Member Development area encompasses four key components and all them vital. First Recruit since our organization is based on membership requirements it’s important that we replace those that no longer meet our requirements to be members.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jaycees and Politics</title>
      <link>http://www.gogorichie.com/posts/jci/jaycees-and-politics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gogorichie.com/posts/jci/jaycees-and-politics/</guid>
      <description>As Jaycee members we have a long history of driving change in our communities across the country and all through our grassroots skills and efforts. For example, when a group of young business men in the Los Angeles area were dissatisfied with their representation in congress they sought out a candidate and came across a young who was a Jaycee their first reaction was here is a young man who has been through the best training in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Founding Of The Abbeville Jaycees</title>
      <link>http://www.gogorichie.com/posts/jci/abbeville-jaycees/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gogorichie.com/posts/jci/abbeville-jaycees/</guid>
      <description>Over the weekend I read another chapter of the book Young Men Can Change The World. I came across another great story this one of how the Abbeville Jaycees was founded. The story was a recount of the adventure of at the time U.S. Jaycees National Vice President Robert E. Condon who at the age of 29 also held the position of civil defense commissioner for the greater New York metro area.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Remember To Vote</title>
      <link>http://www.gogorichie.com/posts/jci/remember-to-vote/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gogorichie.com/posts/jci/remember-to-vote/</guid>
      <description>I was reading a section of a Book called Young Men Can Change The World the other day and wanted to share it with you. It told the story of group Jaycee members out in California who were so passionate with some the legislation being passed in their community that they put together a committee to find someone from their community to run for Representative. After months of searching they found a young Jaycee member who was a lawyer and encouraged him to run, with their support and determination not to lose he went on to win and get elected.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
